<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="ath0_main_text">You make your way to weights class. Today is the first day, so you need to figure out your maxes for each lift. First up, benchpress. How much weight do you start out with on?</string>
    <string name="ath0_option1">100 lbs.</string>
    <string name="ath0_option2">150 lbs.</string>
    <string name="ath0_option3">200 lbs.</string>

    <string name="ath1_main_text">You put on the weights. You position yourself on the bench and lift the bar off the rack. Immediately, it falls onto your chest. You must have mixed up the weights! You never were very smart. As you struggle to breath, adrenaline rushes through your veins. You feel a strength unbeknownst to you before. You manage to lift the weight off of your chest, saving your life. What do you do next?</string>
    <string name="ath1_option1">Get a drink</string>
    <string name="ath1_option2">Runaway from this dumb class</string>
    <string name="ath1_option3">Rampage with this new strength</string>

    <string name="ath2_main_text">You walk towards the drinking fountain and some dumb kid drops a dumbbell on your foot. </string>
    <string name="ath2_option1">You got the broken foot ending</string>
    <string name="ath2_option2">You got the broken foot ending</string>
    <string name="ath2_option3">You got the broken foot ending</string>

    <string name="ath3_main_text">You run from the school and across the street. Unfortunately, the adrenaline has dulled your senses. You are hit by a car.</string>
    <string name="ath3_option1">You got the death by car ending</string>
    <string name="ath3_option2">You got the death by car ending</string>
    <string name="ath3_option3">You got the death by car ending</string>

    <string name="ath4_main_text">You run from the school and into the street. You feel invincible. You run at the oncoming traffic preparing to obliterate it. Unfortunately, you are not invincible. You are pancaked.</string>
    <string name="ath4_option1">You got the death by stupidity ending</string>
    <string name="ath4_option2">You got the death by stupidity ending</string>
    <string name="ath4_option3">You got the death by stupidity ending</string>
</resources>
