<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="int0_main_text">You have always been a good problem solver and love to learn new things, so intelligence classes seemed like the best option for you. You head to your first class of the day. Computer Science 101. You are early so you decide to open up your laptop read the daily news. Everywhere you look is saying the same thing. The world is being hacked.  Chaos erupts! The secret government organizations have failed. Suddenly, the screen goes dark and dots begin to appear. You recognize the path immediately. It leads to a hidden pier you enjoy studying at sometimes. </string>
    <string name="int0_option1">Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int0_option2">Stay in Class.</string>
    <string name="int0_option3">Leave class to see if you can find who sent you the message. </string>
    <string name="int1_main_text">Your curiosity gets the best of you. You cannot help but follow the path to the pier. When you get there, two boats are waiting on the shore.</string>
    <string name="int1_option1">Get in the white fishing boat.</string>
    <string name="int1_option2">Walk to the small grey boat.</string>
    <string name="int1_option3">You are not much of the thieving type. You look around for another clue.</string>
    <string name="int2_main_text">You decide to be responsible and listen to your first class, but that note is still nagging at you. It doesn\'t help that then end of the world is all anybody is talking about. When the teacher starts the lecture, you try to take some notes on your laptop, but you can\'t seem to navigate anywhere but the map to the pier. </string>
    <string name="int2_option1">Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int2_option2">Stay in class.</string>
    <string name="int2_option3">Head to the nearest emergency shelter. </string>
    <string name="int3_main_text">You decide to investigate this clue a little more. You wouldn\'t want to be the one to jump to conclusions. Anyway, everyone has heard about the recent emergency and no one else\'s laptops have been taken hostage by a map. </string>
    <string name="int3_option1">Go talk to your friend about the note.</string>
    <string name="int3_option2">Go talk to your roommate about the note.</string>
    <string name="int3_option3">Go talk to the IT guy.</string>
    <string name="int4_main_text">You decide to get in the white boat. It is a fishing boat and it looks fairly sturdy, safe, and reliable. You feel great about your choice until a man walks towards you. He is shouting, but you can\'t quite tell what he is saying. He gets closer and you realize that this is his boat! Oops!</string>
    <string name="int4_option1">Jump out of the boat and apologize to the man. </string>
    <string name="int4_option2">Turn the boat on and speed away as quickly as possible. </string>
    <string name="int4_option3">Get out of the boat and explain your situation to the man.</string><string name="int5_main_text">The grey boat sounds like the right option to you. After all, grey has always been your favorite color. You walk to the boat, but it seems a little sketchy, not quite the safety you were looking for.</string>
    <string name="int5_option1"> Start the boat anyway and take off.</string>
    <string name="int5_option2">Get out of the boat and go to the white boat.</string>
    <string name="int5_option3">Get out of the boat and look for another option. </string><string name="int6_main_text">You have searched for what seems like forever and cannot for the life of you figure out another option. You know that you have no choice but to get on a boat.</string>
    <string name="int6_option1">Go back to the white boat.</string>
    <string name="int6_option2">Go back to the grey boat.</string>
    <string name="int6_option3">Use supplies you find on the beach to build a raft yourself. </string><string name="int7_main_text">You tried to take the beaten path, but you couldn\'t help it! The safe option just didn\'t work out this time. You know that it is time to step out of your comfort zone. </string>
    <string name="int7_option1"> Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int7_option2">Investigate the Note.</string>
    <string name="int7_option3"></string>
    <string name="int8_main_text">Your friend is quite intrigued about the note. He thinks that it might be a little risky, but you should definitely follow the path. What\'s the worst that can happen?</string>
    <string name="int8_option1">Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int8_option2">Go back to investigating the note.</string>
    <string name="int8_option3">Go back to class</string>
    <string name="int9_main_text">Your roommate sheds some light on the note. She notices that new dots appear as you walk around campus that lead you to the pier. She thinks you should go down the the pier and investigate more there.</string>
    <string name="int9_option1">Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int9_option2">Go back to investigating the note.</string>
    <string name="int9_option3">Go back to class</string>
    <string name="int10_main_text">You are hoping that the IT guy Steve can shed some light on what happened to your computer, but he is a bit crazier than you remember and is a bit scary. When he analyzes your laptop, he finds that there are additional dots that are waiting to appear, but he doesn\'t know where they need to go. He suggests that you go to the pier to see if you can find out. </string>
    <string name="int10_option1">Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int10_option2">Go back to investigating the note.</string>
    <string name="int10_option3">Go back to class.</string>
    <string name="int11_main_text">The man graciously accepts your apology and you explain to him your situation. He offers you a ride in his boat. </string>
    <string name="int11_option1">Take him up on the offer.</string>
    <string name="int11_option2"> Try the grey boat instead.</string>
    <string name="int11_option3">Look around for another option.</string>
    <string name="int12_main_text">You regret that you had to end up stealing a boat, but you know that it is necessary to save the world. Unfortunately, it seems that karma doesn\'t agree with you. The boat ran out of fuel, but you see what may be an island near by. </string>
    <string name="int12_option1">Go back to shore and get in the grey boat.</string>
    <string name="int12_option2"> Paddle to the nearby island.</string>
    <string name="int12_option3"></string>
    <string name="int13_main_text">You wish that the boat you took was in better conditions. Especially when you get out a few miles and your boat breaks. Thankfully, you notice an island not too far from where you are.</string>
    <string name="int13_option1">Find your way back to shore and get in the white boat. </string>
    <string name="int13_option2">Paddle to the nearby island.</string>
    <string name="int13_option3"></string>
    <string name="int14_main_text">The man did not know the sea as well as you thought he might. You are feel pretty lost, but you think you see an island in the distance.</string>
    <string name="int14_option1"> Find your way back to shore and get in the grey boat. </string>
    <string name="int14_option2">Paddle to the nearby island.</string>
    <string name="int14_option3"></string>
    <string name="int15_main_text">When you get to the island, it seems magical. You decide to do some exploring and see if you can make any new dots appear. </string>
    <string name="int15_option1">Go Left.</string>
    <string name="int15_option2">Go right.</string>
    <string name="int15_option3">Go straight.</string>
    <string name="int16_main_text">That seems to be the right direction. At least it did until everything around you seemed to start growing. You realize that you are falling through a sinkhole. The more you try to get out the farther you fall. This is the end. But it wasn\'t. You have entered an entirely new world. You are startled by a voice coming from behind you. He informs you that he is your dux ducis (whatever that means) and he has been sent to help you save the world. He provides a hint to help you with your mission. Resist temptation, whatever that means. Just then, you see a young boy in the distance. </string>
    <string name="int16_option1">Approach the boy.</string>
    <string name="int16_option2">Spy on the boy.</string>
    <string name="int16_option3">Walk around the boy.</string>
    <string name="int17_main_text">When you approach the boy he gives you a riddle. I am a number with a couple of friends, quarter a dozen, and you\'ll find me again. What am I? You answer...</string>
    <string name="int17_option1">three.</string>
    <string name="int17_option2">four.</string>
    <string name="int17_option3">twenty-five.</string>
    <string name="int18_main_text">You decide to climb a tall tree to get a better visual of the boy. You realize that he is whittling some bark. You decide to get a little closer and you realize that the image he is carving looks very similar to the map on your computer. </string>
    <string name="int18_option1">Steal the bark from the boy. </string>
    <string name="int18_option2">Talk to the boy.</string>
    <string name="int18_option3">Go around the boy.</string>
    <string name="int19_main_text">After going around the boy, you realize that you are completely lost. You wish you had more direction, but at this point all hope is lost. </string>
    <string name="int19_option1">YOU GOT THE LOST IN THE FOREST ENDING. </string>
    <string name="int19_option2"></string>
    <string name="int19_option3"></string>
    <string name="int20_main_text">You must be quite the mastermind, because you solved the riddle! The boy was pleased with your answer and decided to give you the piece of bark he was carving. You match the drawing to your map and realize that it has additional paths on it. </string>
    <string name="int20_option1">Follow the new path. </string>
    <string name="int20_option2">Ask the boy to come on your journey with you. </string>
    <string name="int20_option3"> Continue on the old path. </string>
    <string name="int21_main_text">You failed to figure out the riddle. Lucky for you, the boy decides to give you one more shot. An apple is 40 cents, a banana is 60 cents and a grapefruit is 80 cents. How much is a pear? You answer...</string>
    <string name="int21_option1">40 cents. </string>
    <string name="int21_option2">1 dollar.</string>
    <string name="int21_option3">20 cents.</string>
    <string name="int22_main_text">You decide to steal the bark from the boy. It is after all the fastest way to continue on your journey. And you are completely justified because you are trying to save the world. Right?</string>
    <string name="int22_option1">Absolutely. No regrets. </string>
    <string name="int22_option2">It\'s fine, but I might feel bad about it later. </string>
    <string name="int22_option3">I just broke every moral bone in my body. </string>
    <string name="int23_main_text">This piece of bark is definitely the next piece of the puzzle. You decide to follow its clues. It takes you to the edge of a forest. The map leads you around the forest, but you see that there is a shortcut through the woods. </string>
    <string name="int23_option1">Trust in the map.</string>
    <string name="int23_option2">Take the shortcut.</string>
    <string name="int23_option3">Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int24_main_text">The boy is surprised by your offer! Nobody has ever invited him to be apart of the action before. He graciously accepts and you realize that he is actually quite helpful. As you follow the new map, you are lead to a forest. The map wants you to go around the forest, but there is a clear shortcut through. </string>
    <string name="int24_option1">Trust in the map. </string>
    <string name="int24_option2">Take the shortcut. </string>
    <string name="int24_option3">Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int25_main_text">As you continue on your previous pathway, you hear a voice from behind you. It is dux ducis, your guide. He asks you why you haven\'t been following the clues he has left you. He thinks you may not have been the right person for the job. </string>
    <string name="int25_option1">Convince him you are the right person.</string>
    <string name="int25_option2">Start on the new path right away.</string>
    <string name="int25_option3"></string>
    <string name="int26_main_text">Phew! You figured that one out. I was a little bit worried for a minute. The boy accepts your answer and decided to give you the piece of bark he was carving. You match the drawing to your map and realize that it has additional paths on it.  </string>
    <string name="int26_option1">Follow the new path. </string>
    <string name="int26_option2">Ask the boy to come on your journey with you. </string>
    <string name="int26_option3">Continue on the old path.</string>
    <string name="int27_main_text">Oops! Wrong again. You fell through a trap door and died. </string>
    <string name="int27_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int27_option2"></string>
    <string name="int27_option3"></string>
    <string name="int28_main_text">Well aren\'t you quite the criminal....After running away from the boy, you match the drawing to your map and realize that it has additional paths on it. </string>
    <string name="int28_option1">Follow the new path.</string>
    <string name="int28_option2">Continue on the old path. </string>
    <string name="int28_option3"> Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int29_main_text">You feel a little bit bad about stealing the bark from the boy, but you believe that you made the right choice. It is better to ask forgiveness later than waste time asking permission first, right?  You match the drawing to your map and realize that it has additional paths on it. </string>
    <string name="int29_option1"> Follow the new path. </string>
    <string name="int29_option2">Continue on the old path.</string>
    <string name="int29_option3">Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int30_main_text">Stealing was definitely the wrong option!! What are you going to do!!! You have never been the criminal type!!! You rush back to the boy and give him his bark back. You apologize and explain why you stole from him in the first place. He is very interested in your situation and offers you the drawing. You thank him and graciously accept. When you take a closer look at the map you match the drawing to your map and realize that it has additional paths on it. </string>
    <string name="int30_option1">Follow the new path. </string>
    <string name="int30_option2">Ask the boy to come on your journey with you. </string>
    <string name="int30_option3">Continue on the old path. </string>
    <string name="int31_main_text">You decide to trust in the map. It probably knows much more than you do anyway. You make it around the forest faster than you thought you would and you arrive at a crossroad. </string>
    <string name="int31_option1"> Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int31_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int31_option3">Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int32_main_text">You decide to be a little reckless and take the shortcut through the forest. When you think that you are about halfway through the forest, your surroundings begin to change. It seems like you are entering an entirely different world. While you are busy looking around, you run into a boulder. On it, there is a pair of drumsticks.  </string>
    <string name="int32_option1"> Pick up the drumsticks.</string>
    <string name="int32_option2"> Run out of the forest as fast as you can.  </string>
    <string name="int32_option3">Take your time exploring the forest. </string>
    <string name="int33_main_text">You use your amazing persuasive speaking skills to reaffirm dux ducis and yourself that you can be a hero. You decide to follow its clues on the piece of bark. It takes you to the edge of a forest. The map leads you around the forest, but you see that there is a shortcut through the woods. </string>
    <string name="int33_option1"> Trust in the map.</string>
    <string name="int33_option2"> Take the shortcut.</string>
    <string name="int33_option3">Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int34_main_text">A break was just what you needed. It gave you a chance to rest up and realize that you haven\'t eaten since this morning. You are quite hungry and decide to look for some food. </string>
    <string name="int34_option1">Pick the berries on the nearby bush.</string>
    <string name="int34_option2"> Kill a nearby bunny. </string>
    <string name="int34_option3"> Spear a fish in the stream. </string>
    <string name="int35_main_text">You and the boy decide to trust in the map. It gives you a chance to get to know each other. He informs you that his name is Ralph. After asking a few questions, you figure out that he can tell the future. You arrive at the end of the forest faster than you thought you would and come to a crossroad. </string>
    <string name="int35_option1"> Take a break. </string>
    <string name="int35_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int35_option3">Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int36_main_text">As you and the boy start your journey through the forest, you are able to learn a little bit more about him. His name is Ralph and he is a psychic. When you think that you are about halfway through the forest, your surroundings begin to change. It seems like you are entering an entirely different world. While you are busy looking around, you run into a boulder. On it, there is a pair of drumsticks. </string>
    <string name="int36_option1"> Pick up the drumsticks.</string>
    <string name="int36_option2">Run out of the forest as fast as you can. </string>
    <string name="int36_option3">Take your time exploring the forest. </string>
    <string name="int37_main_text">You decide to take a break and get to know your new companion. You find out his name is Ralph and he is a psychic. You then realize that you haven\'t eaten since this morning. You are quite hungry and decide to look for some food. </string>
    <string name="int37_option1"> Pick some berries. </string>
    <string name="int37_option2">Kill a bunny. </string>
    <string name="int37_option3">Spear a fish in the stream.</string>
    <string name="int38_main_text">As you continue wandering along your path, you come across a river. </string>
    <string name="int38_option1">Cross the narrow spot in the river.</string>
    <string name="int38_option2">Cross the widest spot of the river.</string>
    <string name="int38_option3">Cut down a tree to make a bridge. </string>
    <string name="int39_main_text">You pick up the drumsticks and suddenly, everything changes. You are in an entirely different world!</string>
    <string name="int39_option1"> Stay in the musician\'s world. </string>
    <string name="int39_option2"> Go back to your pre-drumstick position.</string>
    <string name="int39_option3">Jump to the end of your world\'s forest. </string>
    <string name="int40_main_text">After running, and running, and running as fast as you can you eventually make it out of the forest. You then come upon a crossroad. </string>
    <string name="int40_option1">Take a break. </string>
    <string name="int40_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int40_option3">Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int41_main_text">Drumsticks!?! In the middle of the forest? That is a little bit odd. You decide to do some exploring and come across another wanderer doing the same thing.</string>
    <string name="int41_option1">Approach the wanderer. </string>
    <string name="int41_option2">Continue wandering through the forest.</string>
    <string name="int41_option3">Take a break. </string>
    <string name="int42_main_text">You pick a handful of berries from a nearby bush and eat them. They are the best thing you have ever tasted!! </string>
    <string name="int42_option1">Eat more berries. </string>
    <string name="int42_option2">Continue walking. </string>
    <string name="int42_option3"></string>
    <string name="int43_main_text">You carefully use your hunting skills to sneak behind the bunny. You snap its neck with your own two hands. You start a fire and cook your food. You never knew bunnies could taste so good.</string>
    <string name="int43_option1">Find another bunny to kill. </string>
    <string name="int43_option2">Continue walking. </string>
    <string name="int43_option3"></string>
    <string name="int44_main_text">You take your time and find a sharp rock and carefully tie it to a stick. You wade into the river and silently watch for a fish. As one swims by you stab it right in the eye. It dies instantly. You build a fire and cook it. You never knew fish could taste so good.</string>
    <string name="int44_option1">Find another fish to spear. </string>
    <string name="int44_option2">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int44_option3"></string>
    <string name="int45_main_text">You and Ralph decide that it is due time for a break and it was just what you needed. It gave you a chance to rest up and realize that you haven\'t eaten since this morning. You are quite hungry and decide to look for some food. </string>
    <string name="int45_option1">Pick some berries.</string>
    <string name="int45_option2">Kill a bunny. </string>
    <string name="int45_option3">Spear a fish in the stream.</string>
    <string name="int46_main_text">As you continue wandering along your path, you come across a river.</string>
    <string name="int46_option1">Cross the narrow spot in the river.</string>
    <string name="int46_option2">Cross the widest spot of the river.</string>
    <string name="int46_option3">Cut down a tree to make a bridge. </string>
    <string name="int47_main_text">After running, and running, and running as fast as you can you eventually make it out of the forest. You then come upon a crossroad. </string>
    <string name="int47_option1"> Take a break. </string>
    <string name="int47_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int47_option3">Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int48_main_text">You and Ralph decide to do some exploring around the forest. You don\'t really see anything too interesting. As you continue wandering along your path, you come across a river.</string>
    <string name="int48_option1">Cross the narrow spot in the river.</string>
    <string name="int48_option2">Cross the widest spot of the river.</string>
    <string name="int48_option3">Cut down a tree to make a bridge. </string>
    <string name="int49_main_text">You pick a handful of berries from a nearby bush and eat them. They are the best thing you have ever tasted!! </string>
    <string name="int49_option1">Eat more berries. </string>
    <string name="int49_option2"> Continue walking. </string>
    <string name="int49_option3"></string>
    <string name="int50_main_text">You carefully use your hunting skills to sneak behind the bunny. You snap its neck with your own two hands. You start a fire and cook your food. You never knew bunnies could taste so good.</string>
    <string name="int50_option1">Find another bunny to kill. </string>
    <string name="int50_option2">Continue walking. </string>
    <string name="int50_option3"></string>
    <string name="int51_main_text">You take your time and find a sharp rock and carefully tie it to a stick. You wade into the river and silently watch for a fish. As one swims by you stab it right in the eye. It dies instantly. You build a fire and cook it. You never knew fish could taste so good.</string>
    <string name="int51_option1">Find another fish to spear. </string>
    <string name="int51_option2">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int51_option3"></string>
    <string name="int52_main_text">You decide to cross the narrow part of the river because you think that it is the fastest way across the river. Unfortunately, it was also the deepest. As you waded farther into the water, your foot got caught in a sinkhole. The current got stronger and pushed you under the water. You drowned. </string>
    <string name="int52_option1">YOU DROWNED. </string>
    <string name="int52_option2"></string>
    <string name="int52_option3"></string>
    <string name="int53_main_text">You successfully make it across the river, but now you are sopping wet. You decide to take a break and let your shoes dry out. When you take off your shoes, a wrinkled up index card falls out. On it is the next piece of the puzzle. When you reach the end of the dots, you are standing at the mouth of a cave. </string>
    <string name="int53_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int53_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int53_option3"></string>
    <string name="int54_main_text">You decide that the best way to make it across the river is to use a tree as a bridge. You go to cut one down but soon realize that you don\'t have a saw. </string>
    <string name="int54_option1">Build a saw.</string>
    <string name="int54_option2">Look for a fallen tree.</string>
    <string name="int54_option3">Go back to the river.</string>
    <string name="int55_main_text">You decide to approach the wanderer. You exchange information and find out his name is Ralph. You tell him about your journey and he is very intrigued. </string>
    <string name="int55_option1">Tell the wanderer goodbye.</string>
    <string name="int55_option2"> Invite the wanderer to come with you. </string>
    <string name="int55_option3">Walk away from the wanderer. </string>
    <string name="int56_main_text">You decide to ignore both the drumsticks and the wanderer. Resist temptations right? You quickly make it through the forest and arrive at a crossroad. </string>
    <string name="int56_option1">Take a break. </string>
    <string name="int56_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int56_option3"> Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int57_main_text">You keep eating berry after berry. Suddenly, the berries develop a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat them. </string>
    <string name="int57_option1"> Continue eating. </string>
    <string name="int57_option2"> Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int57_option3">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int58_main_text">You begin walking on your trek again. You walk and walk until you arrive at the mouth of a cave. </string>
    <string name="int58_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int58_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int58_option3"></string>
    <string name="int59_main_text">You kill and cook another bunny. Suddenly, it develops a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat it.</string>
    <string name="int59_option1">Continue eating.</string>
    <string name="int59_option2"> Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int59_option3">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int60_main_text">You kill and cook another fish. Suddenly, it develops a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat it.</string>
    <string name="int60_option1"> Continue eating. </string>
    <string name="int60_option2">Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int60_option3">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int61_main_text">You continue to eat the food you had collected. You die of a poison overdose.</string>
    <string name="int61_option1">YOU DIED.</string>
    <string name="int61_option2"></string>
    <string name="int61_option3"></string>
    <string name="int62_main_text">You successfully make it across the river, but now you are sopping wet. You decide to take a break and let your shoes dry out. When you take off your shoes, a wrinkled up index card falls out. On it is the next piece of the puzzle. When you reach the end of the dots, you are standing at the mouth of a cave.</string>
    <string name="int62_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int62_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int62_option3"></string>
    <string name="int63_main_text">Thanks to help from Ralph, you are able to cut down a tree and you successfully make it across the river. As you continue walking, you find yourselves standing at the mouth of a cave.</string>
    <string name="int63_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int63_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int63_option3"></string>
    <string name="int64_main_text">You begin walking on your trek again. You walk and walk until you arrive at the mouth of a cave. </string>
    <string name="int64_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int64_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int64_option3"></string>
    <string name="int65_main_text">You keep eating berry after berry. Suddenly, the berries develop a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat them. </string>
    <string name="int65_option1">Continue eating. </string>
    <string name="int65_option2">Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int65_option3">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int66_main_text">You kill and cook another bunny. Suddenly, it develops a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat it.</string>
    <string name="int66_option1">Continue eating.</string>
    <string name="int66_option2">Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int66_option3">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int67_main_text">You kill and cook another fish. Suddenly, it develops a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat it.</string>
    <string name="int67_option1">Continue eating.</string>
    <string name="int67_option2"> Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int67_option3"> Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int68_main_text">You do some scavenging and find some materials to form a makeshift saw. The tree falls and you roll it to the river. You are able to successfully cross. As you continue walking, you find yourselves standing at the mouth of a cave.</string>
    <string name="int68_option1"> Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int68_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int68_option3"></string>
    <string name="int69_main_text">You find a fallen tree and roll it to the river. You are able to successfully cross. As you continue walking, you find yourselves standing at the mouth of a cave.</string>
    <string name="int69_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int69_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int69_option3"></string>
    <string name="int70_main_text">After leaving the wanderer, you quickly make it through the forest and arrive at a crossroad.</string>
    <string name="int70_option1">Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int70_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int70_option3">Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int71_main_text">The wanderer graciously accepts your offer. The two of you quickly make it through the forest. As you continue wandering along your path, you come across a river.</string>
    <string name="int71_option1">Cross the narrow spot in the river.  </string>
    <string name="int71_option2">Cross the widest spot of the river.   </string>
    <string name="int71_option3">Cut down a tree to make a bridge</string>
    <string name="int72_main_text">You desperately search the forest for an antidote. You find some leaves that you recognize from your plant studies class. You crush them up and eat them. But it is too late. Suddenly, your feet start stinging. You rip off your shoes and discover tattoos crawling up your skin. You realize that it is the map. You follow the new dots and arrive at the mouth of a cave. </string>
    <string name="int72_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int72_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int72_option3"></string>
    <string name="int73_main_text">The cave is incredibly dark. As you walk in...you hear a droll voice coming from the shadows. "Come in.." it says. You are startled when the voice begins again. He gives you a riddle. "You are in a pitch dark room and you know that there is a kerosene lamp and a fireplace. You only have one match to light something. What do you light first?"  </string>
    <string name="int73_option1">The lamp.</string>
    <string name="int73_option2">The fireplace.</string>
    <string name="int73_option3">Neither.</string>
    <string name="int74_main_text">You desperately search the forest for an antidote. You find some leaves that you recognize from your plant studies class. You crush them up and eat them. But it is too late. Suddenly, your feet start stinging. You rip off your shoes and discover tattoos crawling up your skin. You realize that it is the map. You follow the new dots and arrive at the mouth of a cave. </string>
    <string name="int74_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int74_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int74_option3"></string>
    <string name="int75_main_text">You decide to go around the cave. After all, there could be bad guys in there. So you continue walking until you eventually arrive at a hut. </string>
    <string name="int75_option1">Go into the hut. </string>
    <string name="int75_option2">Go around the hut. </string>
    <string name="int75_option3"></string>
    <string name="int76_main_text">The cave is incredibly dark. As you walk in...you hear a droll voice coming from the shadows. "Come in.." it says. You are startled when the voice begins again. He gives you a riddle. "You are in a pitch dark room and you know that there is a kerosene lamp and a fireplace. You only have one match to light something. What do you light first?"  </string>
    <string name="int76_option1">The lamp.</string>
    <string name="int76_option2">The fireplace.</string>
    <string name="int76_option3">Neither.</string>
    <string name="int77_main_text">The cave is incredibly dark. As you walk in...you hear a droll voice coming from the shadows. "Come in.." it says. You are startled when the voice begins again. He gives you a riddle. "You are in a pitch dark room and you know that there is a kerosene lamp and a fireplace. You only have one match to light something. What do you light first?"  </string>
    <string name="int77_option1">The lamp.</string>
    <string name="int77_option2">The fireplace.</string>
    <string name="int77_option3">Neither.</string>
    <string name="int78_main_text">The cave is incredibly dark. As you walk in...you hear a droll voice coming from the shadows. "Come in.." it says. You are startled when the voice begins again. He gives you a riddle. "You are in a pitch dark room and you know that there is a kerosene lamp and a fireplace. You only have one match to light something. What do you light first?"  </string>
    <string name="int78_option1">The lamp.</string>
    <string name="int78_option2">The fireplace. </string>
    <string name="int78_option3">Neither.</string>
    <string name="int79_main_text">You must have answered correctly because the voice leads you through narrow passages and deep ponds until you make it to a room lined with weapons of every kind. "Make your choice wisely, for you only get one. One is a savior, the others your done," the voice continues. You decide to pick up a....</string>
    <string name="int79_option1">Sword.</string>
    <string name="int79_option2">Gun.</string>
    <string name="int79_option3">Bow and Arrow.</string>
    <string name="int80_main_text">You must have answered correctly because the voice leads you through narrow passages and deep ponds until you make it to a room lined with weapons of every kind. "Make your choice wisely, for you only get one. One is a savior, the others your done," the voice continues. You decide to pick up a....</string>
    <string name="int80_option1">Sword.</string>
    <string name="int80_option2">Gun.</string>
    <string name="int80_option3">Bow and Arrow.</string>
    <string name="int81_main_text">You must have answered correctly because the voice leads you through narrow passages and deep ponds until you make it to a room lined with weapons of every kind. "Make your choice wisely, for you only get one. One is a savior, the others your done," the voice continues. You decide to pick up a....</string>
    <string name="int81_option1">Sword.</string>
    <string name="int81_option2">Gun.</string>
    <string name="int81_option3">Bow and Arrow.</string>
    <string name="int82_main_text">You must have answered correctly because the voice leads you through narrow passages and deep ponds until you make it to a room lined with weapons of every kind. "Make your choice wisely, for you only get one. One is a savior, the others your done," the voice continues. You decide to pick up a....</string>
    <string name="int82_option1">Sword.</string>
    <string name="int82_option2">Gun.</string>
    <string name="int82_option3">Bow and Arrow.</string>
    <string name="int83_main_text">You are a little worried about what lies ahead of you and you are haunted by the voice in the darkness. You hope you chose the right weapon, but the day is almost over and you really just want to survive the night.  The walking seems to never end. Eventually, the atmosphere seems to have thickened. You can already tell you are in the right place. All of the sudden, you hear a deafening ROAR! A firing dragon descends upon you. </string>
    <string name="int83_option1">Try to make the dragon your friend. </string>
    <string name="int83_option2"> Kill the beast!</string>
    <string name="int83_option3">Give up. You are really tired. </string>
    <string name="int84_main_text">You are a little worried about what lies ahead of you and you are haunted by the voice in the darkness. You hope you chose the right weapon, but the day is almost over and you really just want to survive the night.  The walking seems to never end. Eventually, the atmosphere seems to have thickened. You can already tell you are in the right place. All of the sudden, you hear a deafening ROAR! A firing dragon descends upon you. </string>
    <string name="int84_option1"> Try to make the dragon your friend. </string>
    <string name="int84_option2">Kill the beast!</string>
    <string name="int84_option3">Give up. You are really tired. </string>
    <string name="int85_main_text">You are a little worried about what lies ahead of you and you are haunted by the voice in the darkness. You hope you chose the right weapon, but the day is almost over and you really just want to survive the night.  The walking seems to never end. Eventually, the atmosphere seems to have thickened. You can already tell you are in the right place. All of the sudden, you hear a deafening ROAR! A firing dragon descends upon you. </string>
    <string name="int85_option1">Try to make the dragon your friend.</string>
    <string name="int85_option2">Kill the beast!</string>
    <string name="int85_option3">Give up. You are really tired. </string>
    <string name="int86_main_text">You are a little worried about what lies ahead of you and you are haunted by the voice in the darkness. You hope you chose the right weapon, but the day is almost over and you really just want to survive the night.  The walking seems to never end. Eventually, the atmosphere seems to have thickened. You can already tell you are in the right place. All of the sudden, you hear a deafening ROAR! A firing dragon descends upon you. </string>
    <string name="int86_option1">Try to make the dragon your friend.</string>
    <string name="int86_option2">Kill the beast!</string>
    <string name="int86_option3">Give up. You are really tired. </string>
    <string name="int87_main_text">You carefully walk up to the dragon, but it wasn\'t much help. As you approach the beast, you trip over a tree root and fall directly into the dragon. He is angered and kills you slowly. It is excruciating. </string>
    <string name="int87_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int87_option2"></string>
    <string name="int87_option3"></string>
    <string name="int88_main_text">You skillfully climb a tree and jump down onto the dragon. You use your weapon effectively and succeed in destroying the dragon! You then see statue off in the distance. As you get closer, you find a key inside it. You instantly know that this is what you came for.  You pick up the key and the ground begins to shake. You fall back into your own world and are so glad to be back on the pier. You run to the cities power grids so that you can save the world. You are running so fast that you fail to see the banana peel that was casually laying on the ground. You slip and fall into the ocean, never to be seen again. </string>
    <string name="int88_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int88_option2"></string>
    <string name="int88_option3"></string>
    <string name="int89_main_text">This day has gone on for so long and you are more exhausted than you ever thought a person could be. You give up and the dragon eats you as a midnight snack. </string>
    <string name="int89_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int89_option2"></string>
    <string name="int89_option3"></string>
    <string name="int90_main_text">"Ha, ha, ha." You hear coming from the shadows. You have answered the riddle incorrectly. The bad guys always win. </string>
    <string name="int90_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int90_option2"></string>
    <string name="int90_option3"></string>
    <string name="int91_main_text">You go around. All the sudden, you hear a strange noise coming from behind you. Then a tree comes crashing down and smashes you like a bug. </string>
    <string name="int91_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int91_option2"></string>
    <string name="int91_option3"></string>
    <string name="int92_main_text">The hut is incredibly dark. As you walk in...you hear a droll voice coming from the shadows. "Come in.." it says. You are startled when the voice begins again. He gives you a riddle. "You are in a pitch dark room and you know that there is a kerosene lamp and a fireplace. You only have one match to light something. What do you light first?"  </string>
    <string name="int92_option1">The lamp.</string>
    <string name="int92_option2">The fireplace.</string>
    <string name="int92_option3">Neither.</string>
    <string name="int93_main_text">You must have answered correctly because you hear the door in front of you audibly unlock. When you enter the room, it is lined with weapons of every kind. "Make your choice wisely, for you only get one. One is a savior, the others your done," the voice continues. You decide to pick up a....</string>
    <string name="int93_option1">Sword.</string>
    <string name="int93_option2">Gun.</string>
    <string name="int93_option3">Bow and Arrow.</string>
    <string name="int94_main_text">You carefully walk up to the dragon, but it wasn\'t much help. As you approach the beast, you trip over a tree root and fall directly into the dragon. He is angered and lunges toward you. You begin to prepare yourself for the slow and excrusiating death, but it doesn\'t come. Instead you feel you skin tingling. You realize that the tattoos you had been obtaining were protecting you! You were unstoppable! You kill the dragon! You then see statue off in the distance. As you get closer, you find a key inside it. You instantly know that this is what you came for.  You pick up the key and the ground begins to shake. You fall back into your own world and are so glad to be back on the pier and your tattoos have disappeared. You run to the cities power grids so that you can save the world. You are running so fast that you fail to see the banana peel that was casually laying on the ground. You slip and fall into the ocean, never to be seen again. </string>
    <string name="int94_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int94_option2"></string>
    <string name="int94_option3"></string>
    <string name="int95_main_text">You start to walk up to the dragon and the dragon walks up to you. This looks promising! At least it did.....the dragon was approaching Ralph, who was in fact betraying you this entire time. He had been sent to stop you from saving the world. You are so shocked by this that Ralph was able to use your own weapon against you. You die instantly. </string>
    <string name="int95_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int95_option2"></string>
    <string name="int95_option3"></string>
    <string name="int96_main_text">You start to walk up to the dragon and the dragon walks up to you. This looks promising! At least it did.....the dragon was approaching Ralph, who was in fact betraying you this entire time. He had been sent to stop you from saving the world. You are so shocked by this that Ralph was able to use your own weapon against you. You both thought that you would die instantly.....but you didn\'t. You realize that you skin is glowing and the tattoos you had been obtaining were protecting you. You are invincible! Ralph is so surprised by this that you are able to defeat him. The dragon accepts you as his new master and flys you to a statue off in the distance. As you get closer, you find a key inside it. You instantly know that this is what you came for.  You pick up the key and the ground begins to shake. You fall back into your own world and are so glad to be back on the pier. You run to the cities power grids so that you can save the world. You become a hero and get your own national holiday. </string>
    <string name="int96_option1">You save the world.</string>
    <string name="int96_option2"></string>
    <string name="int96_option3"></string>
    <string name="int97_main_text">This day has gone on for so long and you are more exhausted than you ever thought a person could be. You give up and the dragon lunges to attack you. Then, your skin starts tingling. You realize that the tattoos you have been acquiring are protecting you. You are invincible and easily defeat the dragon. You then see statue off in the distance. As you get closer, you find a key inside it. You instantly know that this is what you came for.  You pick up the key and the ground begins to shake. You fall back into your own world and are so glad to be back on the pier and your tattoos have disappeared. You run to the cities power grids so that you can save the world.You become a hero and get your own national holiday. </string>
    <string name="int97_option1">You save the world. </string>
    <string name="int97_option2"></string>
    <string name="int97_option3"></string>
    <string name="int98_main_text">This day has gone on for so long and you are more exhausted than you ever thought a person could be. You give up. All of the sudden, you feel something on you back, as you reach for it you realize that Ralph has litterally stabbed you in the back and has been conspiring against you this whole time. Even the dragon was a part of his plan. Your skin starts tingling. You realize that the tattoos you have been acquiring are protecting you. You are invincible! Ralph is so surprised by this that you are able to defeat him. The dragon accepts you as his new master and flys you to a statue off in the distance. As you get closer, you find a key inside it. You instantly know that this is what you came for.  You pick up the key and the ground begins to shake. You fall back into your own world and are so glad to be back on the pier. You run to the cities power grids so that you can save the world. You become a hero and get your own national holiday. </string>
    <string name="int98_option1">You save the world!</string>
    <string name="int98_option2"></string>
    <string name="int98_option3"></string>


</resources>
