<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
        <string name="story1_main_text">It\'s the first day of high school. You need to pick your classes. Which do you choose?</string>
        <string name="story1_option1">Computer Science 101</string>
        <string name="story1_option2">Band</string>
        <string name="story1_option3">Weight Training</string>

        <string name="ath0_main_text">You make your way to weights class. Today is the first day, so you need to figure out your maxes for each lift. First up, benchpress. How much weight do you start out with on?</string>
        <string name="ath0_option1">100 lbs.</string>
        <string name="ath0_option2">150 lbs.</string>
        <string name="ath0_option3">200 lbs.</string>

        <string name="ath1_main_text">You put on the weights. You position yourself on the bench and lift the bar off the rack. Immediately, it falls onto your chest. You must have mixed up the weights! You never were very smart. As you struggle to breathe, adrenaline rushes through your veins. You feel a strength unbeknownst to you before. You manage to lift the weight off of your chest, saving your life. What do you do next?</string>
        <string name="ath1_option1">Get a drink</string>
        <string name="ath1_option2">Runaway from this dumb class</string>
        <string name="ath1_option3">Rampage with this new strength</string>

        <string name="ath2_main_text">You walk towards the drinking fountain and some dumb kid drops a dumbbell on your foot. </string>
        <string name="ath2_option1">You got the broken foot ending</string>
        <string name="ath2_option2">You got the broken foot ending</string>
        <string name="ath2_option3">You got the broken foot ending</string>

        <string name="ath3_main_text">You run from the school and across the street. Unfortunately, the adrenaline has dulled your senses. You are hit by a car.</string>
        <string name="ath3_option1">You got the death by car ending</string>
        <string name="ath3_option2">You got the death by car ending</string>
        <string name="ath3_option3">You got the death by car ending</string>

        <string name="ath4_main_text">You run from the school and into the street. You feel invincible. You run at the oncoming traffic preparing to obliterate it. Unfortunately, you are not invincible. You are pancaked.</string>
        <string name="ath4_option1">You got the death by stupidity ending</string>
        <string name="ath4_option2">You got the death by stupidity ending</string>
        <string name="ath4_option3">You got the death by stupidity ending</string>


    <string name="int0_main_text">You have always been a good problem solver and love to learn new things, so intelligence classes seemed like the best option for you. You head to your first class of the day. Computer Science 101. You are early so you decide to open up your laptop read the daily news. Everywhere you look is saying the same thing. The world is being hacked.  Chaos erupts! The secret government organizations have failed. Suddenly, the screen goes dark and dots begin to appear. You recognize the path immediately. It leads to a hidden pier you enjoy studying at sometimes. </string>
    <string name="int0_option1">Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int0_option2">Stay in Class.</string>
    <string name="int0_option3">Leave class to see if you can find who sent you the message. </string>
    <string name="int1_main_text">Your curiosity gets the best of you. You cannot help but follow the path to the pier. When you get there, two boats are waiting on the shore.</string>
    <string name="int1_option1">Get in the white fishing boat.</string>
    <string name="int1_option2">Walk to the small grey boat.</string>
    <string name="int1_option3">You are not much of the thieving type. You look around for another clue.</string>
    <string name="int2_main_text">You decide to be responsible and listen to your first class, but that note is still nagging at you. It doesn\'t help that then end of the world is all anybody is talking about. When the teacher starts the lecture, you try to take some notes on your laptop, but you can\'t seem to navigate anywhere but the map to the pier. </string>
    <string name="int2_option1">Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int2_option2">Stay in class.</string>
    <string name="int2_option3">Head to the nearest emergency shelter. </string>
    <string name="int3_main_text">You decide to investigate this clue a little more. You wouldn\'t want to be the one to jump to conclusions. Anyway, everyone has heard about the recent emergency and no one else\'s laptops have been taken hostage by a map. </string>
    <string name="int3_option1">Go talk to your friend about the note.</string>
    <string name="int3_option2">Go talk to your roommate about the note.</string>
    <string name="int3_option3">Go talk to the IT guy.</string>
    <string name="int4_main_text">You decide to get in the white boat. It is a fishing boat and it looks fairly sturdy, safe, and reliable. You feel great about your choice until a man walks towards you. He is shouting, but you can\'t quite tell what he is saying. He gets closer and you realize that this is his boat! Oops!</string>
    <string name="int4_option1">Jump out of the boat and apologize to the man. </string>
    <string name="int4_option2">Turn the boat on and speed away as quickly as possible. </string>
    <string name="int4_option3">Get out of the boat and explain your situation to the man.</string><string name="int5_main_text">The grey boat sounds like the right option to you. After all, grey has always been your favorite color. You walk to the boat, but it seems a little sketchy, not quite the safety you were looking for.</string>
    <string name="int5_option1"> Start the boat anyway and take off.</string>
    <string name="int5_option2">Get out of the boat and go to the white boat.</string>
    <string name="int5_option3">Get out of the boat and look for another option. </string><string name="int6_main_text">You have searched for what seems like forever and cannot for the life of you figure out another option. You know that you have no choice but to get on a boat.</string>
    <string name="int6_option1">Go back to the white boat.</string>
    <string name="int6_option2">Go back to the grey boat.</string>
    <string name="int6_option3">Use supplies you find on the beach to build a raft yourself. </string><string name="int7_main_text">You tried to take the beaten path, but you couldn\'t help it! The safe option just didn\'t work out this time. You know that it is time to step out of your comfort zone. </string>
    <string name="int7_option1"> Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int7_option2">Investigate the Note.</string>
    <string name="int7_option3"></string>
    <string name="int8_main_text">Your friend is quite intrigued about the note. He thinks that it might be a little risky, but you should definitely follow the path. What\'s the worst that can happen?</string>
    <string name="int8_option1">Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int8_option2">Go back to investigating the note.</string>
    <string name="int8_option3">Go back to class</string>
    <string name="int9_main_text">Your roommate sheds some light on the note. She notices that new dots appear as you walk around campus that lead you to the pier. She thinks you should go down the the pier and investigate more there.</string>
    <string name="int9_option1">Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int9_option2">Go back to investigating the note.</string>
    <string name="int9_option3">Go back to class</string>
    <string name="int10_main_text">You are hoping that the IT guy Steve can shed some light on what happened to your computer, but he is a bit crazier than you remember and is a bit scary. When he analyzes your laptop, he finds that there are additional dots that are waiting to appear, but he doesn\'t know where they need to go. He suggests that you go to the pier to see if you can find out. </string>
    <string name="int10_option1">Go to the pier.</string>
    <string name="int10_option2">Go back to investigating the note.</string>
    <string name="int10_option3">Go back to class.</string>
    <string name="int11_main_text">The man graciously accepts your apology and you explain to him your situation. He offers you a ride in his boat. </string>
    <string name="int11_option1">Take him up on the offer.</string>
    <string name="int11_option2"> Try the grey boat instead.</string>
    <string name="int11_option3">Look around for another option.</string>
    <string name="int12_main_text">You regret that you had to end up stealing a boat, but you know that it is necessary to save the world. Unfortunately, it seems that karma doesn\'t agree with you. The boat ran out of fuel, but you see what may be an island near by. </string>
    <string name="int12_option1">Go back to shore and get in the grey boat.</string>
    <string name="int12_option2"> Paddle to the nearby island.</string>
    <string name="int12_option3"></string>
    <string name="int13_main_text">You wish that the boat you took was in better conditions. Especially when you get out a few miles and your boat breaks. Thankfully, you notice an island not too far from where you are.</string>
    <string name="int13_option1">Find your way back to shore and get in the white boat. </string>
    <string name="int13_option2">Paddle to the nearby island.</string>
    <string name="int13_option3"></string>
    <string name="int14_main_text">The man did not know the sea as well as you thought he might. You are feel pretty lost, but you think you see an island in the distance.</string>
    <string name="int14_option1"> Find your way back to shore and get in the grey boat. </string>
    <string name="int14_option2">Paddle to the nearby island.</string>
    <string name="int14_option3"></string>
    <string name="int15_main_text">When you get to the island, it seems magical. You decide to do some exploring and see if you can make any new dots appear. </string>
    <string name="int15_option1">Go Left.</string>
    <string name="int15_option2">Go right.</string>
    <string name="int15_option3">Go straight.</string>
    <string name="int16_main_text">That seems to be the right direction. At least it did until everything around you seemed to start growing. You realize that you are falling through a sinkhole. The more you try to get out the farther you fall. This is the end. But it wasn\'t. You have entered an entirely new world. You are startled by a voice coming from behind you. He informs you that he is your dux ducis (whatever that means) and he has been sent to help you save the world. He provides a hint to help you with your mission. Resist temptation, whatever that means. Just then, you see a young boy in the distance. </string>
    <string name="int16_option1">Approach the boy.</string>
    <string name="int16_option2">Spy on the boy.</string>
    <string name="int16_option3">Walk around the boy.</string>
    <string name="int17_main_text">When you approach the boy he gives you a riddle. I am a number with a couple of friends, quarter a dozen, and you\'ll find me again. What am I? You answer...</string>
    <string name="int17_option1">three.</string>
    <string name="int17_option2">four.</string>
    <string name="int17_option3">twenty-five.</string>
    <string name="int18_main_text">You decide to climb a tall tree to get a better visual of the boy. You realize that he is whittling some bark. You decide to get a little closer and you realize that the image he is carving looks very similar to the map on your computer. </string>
    <string name="int18_option1">Steal the bark from the boy. </string>
    <string name="int18_option2">Talk to the boy.</string>
    <string name="int18_option3">Go around the boy.</string>
    <string name="int19_main_text">After going around the boy, you realize that you are completely lost. You wish you had more direction, but at this point all hope is lost. </string>
    <string name="int19_option1">YOU GOT THE LOST IN THE FOREST ENDING. </string>
    <string name="int19_option2"></string>
    <string name="int19_option3"></string>
    <string name="int20_main_text">You must be quite the mastermind, because you solved the riddle! The boy was pleased with your answer and decided to give you the piece of bark he was carving. You match the drawing to your map and realize that it has additional paths on it. </string>
    <string name="int20_option1">Follow the new path. </string>
    <string name="int20_option2">Ask the boy to come on your journey with you. </string>
    <string name="int20_option3"> Continue on the old path. </string>
    <string name="int21_main_text">You failed to figure out the riddle. Lucky for you, the boy decides to give you one more shot. An apple is 40 cents, a banana is 60 cents and a grapefruit is 80 cents. How much is a pear? You answer...</string>
    <string name="int21_option1">40 cents. </string>
    <string name="int21_option2">1 dollar.</string>
    <string name="int21_option3">20 cents.</string>
    <string name="int22_main_text">You decide to steal the bark from the boy. It is after all the fastest way to continue on your journey. And you are completely justified because you are trying to save the world. Right?</string>
    <string name="int22_option1">Absolutely. No regrets. </string>
    <string name="int22_option2">It\'s fine, but I might feel bad about it later. </string>
    <string name="int22_option3">I just broke every moral bone in my body. </string>
    <string name="int23_main_text">This piece of bark is definitely the next piece of the puzzle. You decide to follow its clues. It takes you to the edge of a forest. The map leads you around the forest, but you see that there is a shortcut through the woods. </string>
    <string name="int23_option1">Trust in the map.</string>
    <string name="int23_option2">Take the shortcut.</string>
    <string name="int23_option3">Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int24_main_text">The boy is surprised by your offer! Nobody has ever invited him to be apart of the action before. He graciously accepts and you realize that he is actually quite helpful. As you follow the new map, you are lead to a forest. The map wants you to go around the forest, but there is a clear shortcut through. </string>
    <string name="int24_option1">Trust in the map. </string>
    <string name="int24_option2">Take the shortcut. </string>
    <string name="int24_option3">Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int25_main_text">As you continue on your previous pathway, you hear a voice from behind you. It is dux ducis, your guide. He asks you why you haven\'t been following the clues he has left you. He thinks you may not have been the right person for the job. </string>
    <string name="int25_option1">Convince him you are the right person.</string>
    <string name="int25_option2">Start on the new path right away.</string>
    <string name="int25_option3"></string>
    <string name="int26_main_text">Phew! You figured that one out. I was a little bit worried for a minute. The boy accepts your answer and decided to give you the piece of bark he was carving. You match the drawing to your map and realize that it has additional paths on it.  </string>
    <string name="int26_option1">Follow the new path. </string>
    <string name="int26_option2">Ask the boy to come on your journey with you. </string>
    <string name="int26_option3">Continue on the old path.</string>
    <string name="int27_main_text">Oops! Wrong again. You fell through a trap door and died. </string>
    <string name="int27_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int27_option2"></string>
    <string name="int27_option3"></string>
    <string name="int28_main_text">Well aren\'t you quite the criminal....After running away from the boy, you match the drawing to your map and realize that it has additional paths on it. </string>
    <string name="int28_option1">Follow the new path.</string>
    <string name="int28_option2">Continue on the old path. </string>
    <string name="int28_option3"> Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int29_main_text">You feel a little bit bad about stealing the bark from the boy, but you believe that you made the right choice. It is better to ask forgiveness later than waste time asking permission first, right?  You match the drawing to your map and realize that it has additional paths on it. </string>
    <string name="int29_option1"> Follow the new path. </string>
    <string name="int29_option2">Continue on the old path.</string>
    <string name="int29_option3">Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int30_main_text">Stealing was definitely the wrong option!! What are you going to do!!! You have never been the criminal type!!! You rush back to the boy and give him his bark back. You apologize and explain why you stole from him in the first place. He is very interested in your situation and offers you the drawing. You thank him and graciously accept. When you take a closer look at the map you match the drawing to your map and realize that it has additional paths on it. </string>
    <string name="int30_option1">Follow the new path. </string>
    <string name="int30_option2">Ask the boy to come on your journey with you. </string>
    <string name="int30_option3">Continue on the old path. </string>
    <string name="int31_main_text">You decide to trust in the map. It probably knows much more than you do anyway. You make it around the forest faster than you thought you would and you arrive at a crossroad. </string>
    <string name="int31_option1"> Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int31_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int31_option3">Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int32_main_text">You decide to be a little reckless and take the shortcut through the forest. When you think that you are about halfway through the forest, your surroundings begin to change. It seems like you are entering an entirely different world. While you are busy looking around, you run into a boulder. On it, there is a pair of drumsticks.  </string>
    <string name="int32_option1"> Pick up the drumsticks.</string>
    <string name="int32_option2"> Run out of the forest as fast as you can.  </string>
    <string name="int32_option3">Take your time exploring the forest. </string>
    <string name="int33_main_text">You use your amazing persuasive speaking skills to reaffirm dux ducis and yourself that you can be a hero. You decide to follow its clues on the piece of bark. It takes you to the edge of a forest. The map leads you around the forest, but you see that there is a shortcut through the woods. </string>
    <string name="int33_option1"> Trust in the map.</string>
    <string name="int33_option2"> Take the shortcut.</string>
    <string name="int33_option3">Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int34_main_text">A break was just what you needed. It gave you a chance to rest up and realize that you haven\'t eaten since this morning. You are quite hungry and decide to look for some food. </string>
    <string name="int34_option1">Pick the berries on the nearby bush.</string>
    <string name="int34_option2"> Kill a nearby bunny. </string>
    <string name="int34_option3"> Spear a fish in the stream. </string>
    <string name="int35_main_text">You and the boy decide to trust in the map. It gives you a chance to get to know each other. He informs you that his name is Ralph. After asking a few questions, you figure out that he can tell the future. You arrive at the end of the forest faster than you thought you would and come to a crossroad. </string>
    <string name="int35_option1"> Take a break. </string>
    <string name="int35_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int35_option3">Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int36_main_text">As you and the boy start your journey through the forest, you are able to learn a little bit more about him. His name is Ralph and he is a psychic. When you think that you are about halfway through the forest, your surroundings begin to change. It seems like you are entering an entirely different world. While you are busy looking around, you run into a boulder. On it, there is a pair of drumsticks. </string>
    <string name="int36_option1"> Pick up the drumsticks.</string>
    <string name="int36_option2">Run out of the forest as fast as you can. </string>
    <string name="int36_option3">Take your time exploring the forest. </string>
    <string name="int37_main_text">You decide to take a break and get to know your new companion. You find out his name is Ralph and he is a psychic. You then realize that you haven\'t eaten since this morning. You are quite hungry and decide to look for some food. </string>
    <string name="int37_option1"> Pick some berries. </string>
    <string name="int37_option2">Kill a bunny. </string>
    <string name="int37_option3">Spear a fish in the stream.</string>
    <string name="int38_main_text">As you continue wandering along your path, you come across a river. </string>
    <string name="int38_option1">Cross the narrow spot in the river.</string>
    <string name="int38_option2">Cross the widest spot of the river.</string>
    <string name="int38_option3">Cut down a tree to make a bridge. </string>
    <string name="int39_main_text">You pick up the drumsticks and suddenly, everything changes. You are in an entirely different world!</string>
    <string name="int39_option1"> Stay in the musician\'s world. </string>
    <string name="int39_option2"> Go back to your pre-drumstick position.</string>
    <string name="int39_option3">Jump to the end of your world\'s forest. </string>
    <string name="int40_main_text">After running, and running, and running as fast as you can you eventually make it out of the forest. You then come upon a crossroad. </string>
    <string name="int40_option1">Take a break. </string>
    <string name="int40_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int40_option3">Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int41_main_text">Drumsticks!?! In the middle of the forest? That is a little bit odd. You decide to do some exploring and come across another wanderer doing the same thing.</string>
    <string name="int41_option1">Approach the wanderer. </string>
    <string name="int41_option2">Continue wandering through the forest.</string>
    <string name="int41_option3">Take a break. </string>
    <string name="int42_main_text">You pick a handful of berries from a nearby bush and eat them. They are the best thing you have ever tasted!! </string>
    <string name="int42_option1">Eat more berries. </string>
    <string name="int42_option2">Continue walking. </string>
    <string name="int42_option3"></string>
    <string name="int43_main_text">You carefully use your hunting skills to sneak behind the bunny. You snap its neck with your own two hands. You start a fire and cook your food. You never knew bunnies could taste so good.</string>
    <string name="int43_option1">Find another bunny to kill. </string>
    <string name="int43_option2">Continue walking. </string>
    <string name="int43_option3"></string>
    <string name="int44_main_text">You take your time and find a sharp rock and carefully tie it to a stick. You wade into the river and silently watch for a fish. As one swims by you stab it right in the eye. It dies instantly. You build a fire and cook it. You never knew fish could taste so good.</string>
    <string name="int44_option1">Find another fish to spear. </string>
    <string name="int44_option2">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int44_option3"></string>
    <string name="int45_main_text">You and Ralph decide that it is due time for a break and it was just what you needed. It gave you a chance to rest up and realize that you haven\'t eaten since this morning. You are quite hungry and decide to look for some food. </string>
    <string name="int45_option1">Pick some berries.</string>
    <string name="int45_option2">Kill a bunny. </string>
    <string name="int45_option3">Spear a fish in the stream.</string>
    <string name="int46_main_text">As you continue wandering along your path, you come across a river.</string>
    <string name="int46_option1">Cross the narrow spot in the river.</string>
    <string name="int46_option2">Cross the widest spot of the river.</string>
    <string name="int46_option3">Cut down a tree to make a bridge. </string>
    <string name="int47_main_text">After running, and running, and running as fast as you can you eventually make it out of the forest. You then come upon a crossroad. </string>
    <string name="int47_option1"> Take a break. </string>
    <string name="int47_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int47_option3">Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int48_main_text">You and Ralph decide to do some exploring around the forest. You don\'t really see anything too interesting. As you continue wandering along your path, you come across a river.</string>
    <string name="int48_option1">Cross the narrow spot in the river.</string>
    <string name="int48_option2">Cross the widest spot of the river.</string>
    <string name="int48_option3">Cut down a tree to make a bridge. </string>
    <string name="int49_main_text">You pick a handful of berries from a nearby bush and eat them. They are the best thing you have ever tasted!! </string>
    <string name="int49_option1">Eat more berries. </string>
    <string name="int49_option2"> Continue walking. </string>
    <string name="int49_option3"></string>
    <string name="int50_main_text">You carefully use your hunting skills to sneak behind the bunny. You snap its neck with your own two hands. You start a fire and cook your food. You never knew bunnies could taste so good.</string>
    <string name="int50_option1">Find another bunny to kill. </string>
    <string name="int50_option2">Continue walking. </string>
    <string name="int50_option3"></string>
    <string name="int51_main_text">You take your time and find a sharp rock and carefully tie it to a stick. You wade into the river and silently watch for a fish. As one swims by you stab it right in the eye. It dies instantly. You build a fire and cook it. You never knew fish could taste so good.</string>
    <string name="int51_option1">Find another fish to spear. </string>
    <string name="int51_option2">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int51_option3"></string>
    <string name="int52_main_text">You decide to cross the narrow part of the river because you think that it is the fastest way across the river. Unfortunately, it was also the deepest. As you waded farther into the water, your foot got caught in a sinkhole. The current got stronger and pushed you under the water. You drowned. </string>
    <string name="int52_option1">YOU DROWNED. </string>
    <string name="int52_option2"></string>
    <string name="int52_option3"></string>
    <string name="int53_main_text">You successfully make it across the river, but now you are sopping wet. You decide to take a break and let your shoes dry out. When you take off your shoes, a wrinkled up index card falls out. On it is the next piece of the puzzle. When you reach the end of the dots, you are standing at the mouth of a cave. </string>
    <string name="int53_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int53_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int53_option3"></string>
    <string name="int54_main_text">You decide that the best way to make it across the river is to use a tree as a bridge. You go to cut one down but soon realize that you don\'t have a saw. </string>
    <string name="int54_option1">Build a saw.</string>
    <string name="int54_option2">Look for a fallen tree.</string>
    <string name="int54_option3">Go back to the river.</string>
    <string name="int55_main_text">You decide to approach the wanderer. You exchange information and find out his name is Ralph. You tell him about your journey and he is very intrigued. </string>
    <string name="int55_option1">Tell the wanderer goodbye.</string>
    <string name="int55_option2"> Invite the wanderer to come with you. </string>
    <string name="int55_option3">Walk away from the wanderer. </string>
    <string name="int56_main_text">You decide to ignore both the drumsticks and the wanderer. Resist temptations right? You quickly make it through the forest and arrive at a crossroad. </string>
    <string name="int56_option1">Take a break. </string>
    <string name="int56_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int56_option3"> Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int57_main_text">You keep eating berry after berry. Suddenly, the berries develop a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat them. </string>
    <string name="int57_option1"> Continue eating. </string>
    <string name="int57_option2"> Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int57_option3">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int58_main_text">You begin walking on your trek again. You walk and walk until you arrive at the mouth of a cave. </string>
    <string name="int58_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int58_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int58_option3"></string>
    <string name="int59_main_text">You kill and cook another bunny. Suddenly, it develops a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat it.</string>
    <string name="int59_option1">Continue eating.</string>
    <string name="int59_option2"> Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int59_option3">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int60_main_text">You kill and cook another fish. Suddenly, it develops a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat it.</string>
    <string name="int60_option1"> Continue eating. </string>
    <string name="int60_option2">Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int60_option3">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int61_main_text">You continue to eat the food you had collected. You die of a poison overdose.</string>
    <string name="int61_option1">YOU DIED.</string>
    <string name="int61_option2"></string>
    <string name="int61_option3"></string>
    <string name="int62_main_text">You successfully make it across the river, but now you are sopping wet. You decide to take a break and let your shoes dry out. When you take off your shoes, a wrinkled up index card falls out. On it is the next piece of the puzzle. When you reach the end of the dots, you are standing at the mouth of a cave.</string>
    <string name="int62_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int62_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int62_option3"></string>
    <string name="int63_main_text">Thanks to help from Ralph, you are able to cut down a tree and you successfully make it across the river. As you continue walking, you find yourselves standing at the mouth of a cave.</string>
    <string name="int63_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int63_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int63_option3"></string>
    <string name="int64_main_text">You begin walking on your trek again. You walk and walk until you arrive at the mouth of a cave. </string>
    <string name="int64_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int64_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int64_option3"></string>
    <string name="int65_main_text">You keep eating berry after berry. Suddenly, the berries develop a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat them. </string>
    <string name="int65_option1">Continue eating. </string>
    <string name="int65_option2">Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int65_option3">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int66_main_text">You kill and cook another bunny. Suddenly, it develops a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat it.</string>
    <string name="int66_option1">Continue eating.</string>
    <string name="int66_option2">Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int66_option3">Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int67_main_text">You kill and cook another fish. Suddenly, it develops a weird aftertaste. You are worried that you were not supposed to eat it.</string>
    <string name="int67_option1">Continue eating.</string>
    <string name="int67_option2"> Look for a potential antidote for poison.</string>
    <string name="int67_option3"> Continue walking.</string>
    <string name="int68_main_text">You do some scavenging and find some materials to form a makeshift saw. The tree falls and you roll it to the river. You are able to successfully cross. As you continue walking, you find yourselves standing at the mouth of a cave.</string>
    <string name="int68_option1"> Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int68_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int68_option3"></string>
    <string name="int69_main_text">You find a fallen tree and roll it to the river. You are able to successfully cross. As you continue walking, you find yourselves standing at the mouth of a cave.</string>
    <string name="int69_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int69_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int69_option3"></string>
    <string name="int70_main_text">After leaving the wanderer, you quickly make it through the forest and arrive at a crossroad.</string>
    <string name="int70_option1">Take a break.</string>
    <string name="int70_option2">Take the path on the left. </string>
    <string name="int70_option3">Take the path on right.</string>
    <string name="int71_main_text">The wanderer graciously accepts your offer. The two of you quickly make it through the forest. As you continue wandering along your path, you come across a river.</string>
    <string name="int71_option1">Cross the narrow spot in the river.  </string>
    <string name="int71_option2">Cross the widest spot of the river.   </string>
    <string name="int71_option3">Cut down a tree to make a bridge</string>
    <string name="int72_main_text">You desperately search the forest for an antidote. You find some leaves that you recognize from your plant studies class. You crush them up and eat them. But it is too late. Suddenly, your feet start stinging. You rip off your shoes and discover tattoos crawling up your skin. You realize that it is the map. You follow the new dots and arrive at the mouth of a cave. </string>
    <string name="int72_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int72_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int72_option3"></string>
    <string name="int73_main_text">The cave is incredibly dark. As you walk in...you hear a droll voice coming from the shadows. "Come in.." it says. You are startled when the voice begins again. He gives you a riddle. "You are in a pitch dark room and you know that there is a kerosene lamp and a fireplace. You only have one match to light something. What do you light first?"  </string>
    <string name="int73_option1">The lamp.</string>
    <string name="int73_option2">The fireplace.</string>
    <string name="int73_option3">Neither.</string>
    <string name="int74_main_text">You desperately search the forest for an antidote. You find some leaves that you recognize from your plant studies class. You crush them up and eat them. But it is too late. Suddenly, your feet start stinging. You rip off your shoes and discover tattoos crawling up your skin. You realize that it is the map. You follow the new dots and arrive at the mouth of a cave. </string>
    <string name="int74_option1">Enter the cave.</string>
    <string name="int74_option2">Go around the cave.</string>
    <string name="int74_option3"></string>
    <string name="int75_main_text">You decide to go around the cave. After all, there could be bad guys in there. So you continue walking until you eventually arrive at a hut. </string>
    <string name="int75_option1">Go into the hut. </string>
    <string name="int75_option2">Go around the hut. </string>
    <string name="int75_option3"></string>
    <string name="int76_main_text">The cave is incredibly dark. As you walk in...you hear a droll voice coming from the shadows. "Come in.." it says. You are startled when the voice begins again. He gives you a riddle. "You are in a pitch dark room and you know that there is a kerosene lamp and a fireplace. You only have one match to light something. What do you light first?"  </string>
    <string name="int76_option1">The lamp.</string>
    <string name="int76_option2">The fireplace.</string>
    <string name="int76_option3">Neither.</string>
    <string name="int77_main_text">The cave is incredibly dark. As you walk in...you hear a droll voice coming from the shadows. "Come in.." it says. You are startled when the voice begins again. He gives you a riddle. "You are in a pitch dark room and you know that there is a kerosene lamp and a fireplace. You only have one match to light something. What do you light first?"  </string>
    <string name="int77_option1">The lamp.</string>
    <string name="int77_option2">The fireplace.</string>
    <string name="int77_option3">Neither.</string>
    <string name="int78_main_text">The cave is incredibly dark. As you walk in...you hear a droll voice coming from the shadows. "Come in.." it says. You are startled when the voice begins again. He gives you a riddle. "You are in a pitch dark room and you know that there is a kerosene lamp and a fireplace. You only have one match to light something. What do you light first?"  </string>
    <string name="int78_option1">The lamp.</string>
    <string name="int78_option2">The fireplace. </string>
    <string name="int78_option3">Neither.</string>
    <string name="int79_main_text">You must have answered correctly because the voice leads you through narrow passages and deep ponds until you make it to a room lined with weapons of every kind. "Make your choice wisely, for you only get one. One is a savior, the others your done," the voice continues. You decide to pick up a....</string>
    <string name="int79_option1">Sword.</string>
    <string name="int79_option2">Gun.</string>
    <string name="int79_option3">Bow and Arrow.</string>
    <string name="int80_main_text">You must have answered correctly because the voice leads you through narrow passages and deep ponds until you make it to a room lined with weapons of every kind. "Make your choice wisely, for you only get one. One is a savior, the others your done," the voice continues. You decide to pick up a....</string>
    <string name="int80_option1">Sword.</string>
    <string name="int80_option2">Gun.</string>
    <string name="int80_option3">Bow and Arrow.</string>
    <string name="int81_main_text">You must have answered correctly because the voice leads you through narrow passages and deep ponds until you make it to a room lined with weapons of every kind. "Make your choice wisely, for you only get one. One is a savior, the others your done," the voice continues. You decide to pick up a....</string>
    <string name="int81_option1">Sword.</string>
    <string name="int81_option2">Gun.</string>
    <string name="int81_option3">Bow and Arrow.</string>
    <string name="int82_main_text">You must have answered correctly because the voice leads you through narrow passages and deep ponds until you make it to a room lined with weapons of every kind. "Make your choice wisely, for you only get one. One is a savior, the others your done," the voice continues. You decide to pick up a....</string>
    <string name="int82_option1">Sword.</string>
    <string name="int82_option2">Gun.</string>
    <string name="int82_option3">Bow and Arrow.</string>
    <string name="int83_main_text">You are a little worried about what lies ahead of you and you are haunted by the voice in the darkness. You hope you chose the right weapon, but the day is almost over and you really just want to survive the night.  The walking seems to never end. Eventually, the atmosphere seems to have thickened. You can already tell you are in the right place. All of the sudden, you hear a deafening ROAR! A firing dragon descends upon you. </string>
    <string name="int83_option1">Try to make the dragon your friend. </string>
    <string name="int83_option2"> Kill the beast!</string>
    <string name="int83_option3">Give up. You are really tired. </string>
    <string name="int84_main_text">You are a little worried about what lies ahead of you and you are haunted by the voice in the darkness. You hope you chose the right weapon, but the day is almost over and you really just want to survive the night.  The walking seems to never end. Eventually, the atmosphere seems to have thickened. You can already tell you are in the right place. All of the sudden, you hear a deafening ROAR! A firing dragon descends upon you. </string>
    <string name="int84_option1"> Try to make the dragon your friend. </string>
    <string name="int84_option2">Kill the beast!</string>
    <string name="int84_option3">Give up. You are really tired. </string>
    <string name="int85_main_text">You are a little worried about what lies ahead of you and you are haunted by the voice in the darkness. You hope you chose the right weapon, but the day is almost over and you really just want to survive the night.  The walking seems to never end. Eventually, the atmosphere seems to have thickened. You can already tell you are in the right place. All of the sudden, you hear a deafening ROAR! A firing dragon descends upon you. </string>
    <string name="int85_option1">Try to make the dragon your friend.</string>
    <string name="int85_option2">Kill the beast!</string>
    <string name="int85_option3">Give up. You are really tired. </string>
    <string name="int86_main_text">You are a little worried about what lies ahead of you and you are haunted by the voice in the darkness. You hope you chose the right weapon, but the day is almost over and you really just want to survive the night.  The walking seems to never end. Eventually, the atmosphere seems to have thickened. You can already tell you are in the right place. All of the sudden, you hear a deafening ROAR! A firing dragon descends upon you. </string>
    <string name="int86_option1">Try to make the dragon your friend.</string>
    <string name="int86_option2">Kill the beast!</string>
    <string name="int86_option3">Give up. You are really tired. </string>
    <string name="int87_main_text">You carefully walk up to the dragon, but it wasn\'t much help. As you approach the beast, you trip over a tree root and fall directly into the dragon. He is angered and kills you slowly. It is excruciating. </string>
    <string name="int87_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int87_option2"></string>
    <string name="int87_option3"></string>
    <string name="int88_main_text">You skillfully climb a tree and jump down onto the dragon. You use your weapon effectively and succeed in destroying the dragon! You then see statue off in the distance. As you get closer, you find a key inside it. You instantly know that this is what you came for.  You pick up the key and the ground begins to shake. You fall back into your own world and are so glad to be back on the pier. You run to the cities power grids so that you can save the world. You are running so fast that you fail to see the banana peel that was casually laying on the ground. You slip and fall into the ocean, never to be seen again. </string>
    <string name="int88_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int88_option2"></string>
    <string name="int88_option3"></string>
    <string name="int89_main_text">This day has gone on for so long and you are more exhausted than you ever thought a person could be. You give up and the dragon eats you as a midnight snack. </string>
    <string name="int89_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int89_option2"></string>
    <string name="int89_option3"></string>
    <string name="int90_main_text">"Ha, ha, ha." You hear coming from the shadows. You have answered the riddle incorrectly. The bad guys always win. </string>
    <string name="int90_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int90_option2"></string>
    <string name="int90_option3"></string>
    <string name="int91_main_text">You go around. All the sudden, you hear a strange noise coming from behind you. Then a tree comes crashing down and smashes you like a bug. </string>
    <string name="int91_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int91_option2"></string>
    <string name="int91_option3"></string>
    <string name="int92_main_text">The hut is incredibly dark. As you walk in...you hear a droll voice coming from the shadows. "Come in.." it says. You are startled when the voice begins again. He gives you a riddle. "You are in a pitch dark room and you know that there is a kerosene lamp and a fireplace. You only have one match to light something. What do you light first?"  </string>
    <string name="int92_option1">The lamp.</string>
    <string name="int92_option2">The fireplace.</string>
    <string name="int92_option3">Neither.</string>
    <string name="int93_main_text">You must have answered correctly because you hear the door in front of you audibly unlock. When you enter the room, it is lined with weapons of every kind. "Make your choice wisely, for you only get one. One is a savior, the others your done," the voice continues. You decide to pick up a....</string>
    <string name="int93_option1">Sword.</string>
    <string name="int93_option2">Gun.</string>
    <string name="int93_option3">Bow and Arrow.</string>
    <string name="int94_main_text">You carefully walk up to the dragon, but it wasn\'t much help. As you approach the beast, you trip over a tree root and fall directly into the dragon. He is angered and lunges toward you. You begin to prepare yourself for the slow and excrusiating death, but it doesn\'t come. Instead you feel you skin tingling. You realize that the tattoos you had been obtaining were protecting you! You were unstoppable! You kill the dragon! You then see statue off in the distance. As you get closer, you find a key inside it. You instantly know that this is what you came for.  You pick up the key and the ground begins to shake. You fall back into your own world and are so glad to be back on the pier and your tattoos have disappeared. You run to the cities power grids so that you can save the world. You are running so fast that you fail to see the banana peel that was casually laying on the ground. You slip and fall into the ocean, never to be seen again. </string>
    <string name="int94_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int94_option2"></string>
    <string name="int94_option3"></string>
    <string name="int95_main_text">You start to walk up to the dragon and the dragon walks up to you. This looks promising! At least it did.....the dragon was approaching Ralph, who was in fact betraying you this entire time. He had been sent to stop you from saving the world. You are so shocked by this that Ralph was able to use your own weapon against you. You die instantly. </string>
    <string name="int95_option1">You Died.</string>
    <string name="int95_option2"></string>
    <string name="int95_option3"></string>
    <string name="int96_main_text">You start to walk up to the dragon and the dragon walks up to you. This looks promising! At least it did.....the dragon was approaching Ralph, who was in fact betraying you this entire time. He had been sent to stop you from saving the world. You are so shocked by this that Ralph was able to use your own weapon against you. You both thought that you would die instantly.....but you didn\'t. You realize that you skin is glowing and the tattoos you had been obtaining were protecting you. You are invincible! Ralph is so surprised by this that you are able to defeat him. The dragon accepts you as his new master and flys you to a statue off in the distance. As you get closer, you find a key inside it. You instantly know that this is what you came for.  You pick up the key and the ground begins to shake. You fall back into your own world and are so glad to be back on the pier. You run to the cities power grids so that you can save the world. You become a hero and get your own national holiday. </string>
    <string name="int96_option1">You save the world.</string>
    <string name="int96_option2"></string>
    <string name="int96_option3"></string>
    <string name="int97_main_text">This day has gone on for so long and you are more exhausted than you ever thought a person could be. You give up and the dragon lunges to attack you. Then, your skin starts tingling. You realize that the tattoos you have been acquiring are protecting you. You are invincible and easily defeat the dragon. You then see statue off in the distance. As you get closer, you find a key inside it. You instantly know that this is what you came for.  You pick up the key and the ground begins to shake. You fall back into your own world and are so glad to be back on the pier and your tattoos have disappeared. You run to the cities power grids so that you can save the world.You become a hero and get your own national holiday. </string>
    <string name="int97_option1">You save the world. </string>
    <string name="int97_option2"></string>
    <string name="int97_option3"></string>
    <string name="int98_main_text">This day has gone on for so long and you are more exhausted than you ever thought a person could be. You give up. All of the sudden, you feel something on you back, as you reach for it you realize that Ralph has litterally stabbed you in the back and has been conspiring against you this whole time. Even the dragon was a part of his plan. Your skin starts tingling. You realize that the tattoos you have been acquiring are protecting you. You are invincible! Ralph is so surprised by this that you are able to defeat him. The dragon accepts you as his new master and flys you to a statue off in the distance. As you get closer, you find a key inside it. You instantly know that this is what you came for.  You pick up the key and the ground begins to shake. You fall back into your own world and are so glad to be back on the pier. You run to the cities power grids so that you can save the world. You become a hero and get your own national holiday. </string>
    <string name="int98_option1">You save the world!</string>
    <string name="int98_option2"></string>
    <string name="int98_option3"></string>


    <string name="mus0_main_text">You go to your locker after choosing band classes. While you are walking in the hallways, you meet a man named Steve. He seems to be the Janitor, he says hi to you with a creepy smile. </string>
    <string name="mus0_option1">Say Hi back</string>
    <string name="mus0_option2">Hello Steve...</string>
    <string name="mus0_option3">Ignore him</string>

    <string name="mus1_main_text">After you stop by your locker it\'s time for Band class! What do you do?</string>
    <string name="mus1_option1">Go to Band Class</string>
    <string name="mus1_option2"></string>
    <string name="mus1_option3"></string>

    <string name="mus2_main_text">During your Band class the Band teacher hands out a new piece of music called Undertow. You start to notice something different when reading the music, it almost seems like the notes are forming a pathway. The title seems to be turning into a red X. You close your eyes and think that you are seeing things, however when you open them the music has turned into a treasure map of some type. It fascinates you and you stare deeply into every detail of it. You could have sworn it was a music sheet just a second before. You ask to go to the bathroom and bring the map with you. Along the way you run into the creepy Janitor, Steve, you both hit the floor hard and the map flies out of your hand. Steve grabs it and gives it back to you, all the while yelling at you for being stupid and blind. He glances at it while giving it back. You run away from Steve scared for your life. As you reach the bathroom you stop and decide to just go for it. You bust open the door next to the bathroom and head outside.</string>
    <string name="mus2_option1">Hooray!</string>
    <string name="mus2_option2">Uh Oh</string>
    <string name="mus2_option3">Weee!</string>

    <string name="mus3_main_text">You come up on a cat in the forest, it looks helpless. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="mus3_option1">Kick it</string>
    <string name="mus3_option2">Pet it</string>
    <string name="mus3_option3">Feed it your lunch</string>

    <string name="mus4_main_text">The cat dies. Now what monster?</string>
    <string name="mus4_option1">Bury his body</string>
    <string name="mus4_option2">Keep the corpse</string>
    <string name="mus4_option3">Leave him</string>

    <string name="mus5_main_text">The cat purrs but dies of starvation shortly afterwards. At least it enjoyed his last moments. Now what do you do?</string>
    <string name="mus5_option1">Bury his body</string>
    <string name="mus5_option2">Keep the corpse</string>
    <string name="mus5_option3">Leave him</string>

    <string name="mus6_main_text">You set the lunch down and the cat furiously eats it. He becomes your friend shortly afterwards. Do you accept his friendship?</string>
    <string name="mus6_option1">FOR SPARTA!</string>
    <string name="mus6_option2">Of course!</string>
    <string name="mus6_option3">Leave him</string>

    <string name="mus7_main_text">The cat becomes your friend and just in time, a wolf comes upon the both of you. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="mus7_option1">Hide behind the cat</string>
    <string name="mus7_option2">Run away with cat</string>
    <string name="mus7_option3">Leave the cat to deal with it</string>

    <string name="mus8_main_text">You leave the cat and feel guilty about not befriending him. Maybe it\'s for the best. As you walk away you meet a old man looking for his cat, Purtis.</string>
    <string name="mus8_option1">Tell him what happened</string>
    <string name="mus8_option2">Say nothing</string>
    <string name="mus8_option3">NO WITNESSES!</string>

    <string name="mus9_main_text">You have the decency to bury the cat and give him a proper funeral. Afterwards you walk away and see another cat.</string>
    <string name="mus9_option1">Attempt to befriend it</string>
    <string name="mus9_option2">Leave it be</string>
    <string name="mus9_option3">E+qy|}y$</string>

    <string name="mus10_main_text">You figure that the corpse could come in handy. And right as you put the cat in your bag a old man comes upon you and asks if you have seen his cat, Purtis?</string>
    <string name="mus10_option1">Tell him where the corpse is</string>
    <string name="mus10_option2">Say nothing</string>
    <string name="mus10_option3">NO WITNESSES!</string>

    <string name="mus11_main_text">You are sick. What kind of person does this to a helpless cat? Shame on you. Anyways, as you walk away you spot another cat. Now what you cat killer?</string>
    <string name="mus11_option1">Kick it and take its corpse</string>
    <string name="mus11_option2">Attempt to befriend it</string>
    <string name="mus11_option3">Ignore it</string>

    <string name="mus12_main_text">The cat defends you but loses his life in the process. Now what?</string>
    <string name="mus12_option1">Bury his body</string>
    <string name="mus12_option2">Keep the corpse</string>
    <string name="mus12_option3">Leave him</string>

    <string name="mus13_main_text">You and the cat run away but meet an old man looking for his cat. He currently does not see the cat as you talk to him. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="mus13_option1">Hide the cat</string>
    <string name="mus13_option2">Give him the cat</string>
    <string name="mus13_option3">Keep walking</string>

    <string name="mus14_main_text">The man runs towards where the cat was last. You hear him crying.</string>
    <string name="mus14_option1">Feel sorry</string>
    <string name="mus14_option2">Feel guilty</string>
    <string name="mus14_option3">Feel accomplished</string>

    <string name="mus15_main_text">CODEBREAKER!!</string>
    <string name="mus15_option1">j;k5 57</string>
    <string name="mus15_option2">j;k5 57</string>
    <string name="mus15_option3">j;k5 57</string>

    <string name="mus16_main_text">You kill the old man. You are now known as a murderer. Your family disowns you and are hunted by the police everyday. They call you the Mad Maniac Murderer. You live the rest of your life on the run.</string>
    <string name="mus16_option1">You got the bad ending</string>
    <string name="mus16_option2">You got the bad ending</string>
    <string name="mus16_option3">You got the bad ending</string>

    <string name="mus17_main_text">The old man asks for his cat.</string>
    <string name="mus17_option1">Give it to him</string>
    <string name="mus17_option2">Keep walking</string>
    <string name="mus17_option3">NO WITNESSES!</string>

    <string name="mus18_main_text">The cat scratches you and runs off. How do you treat the wound?</string>
    <string name="mus18_option1">Find some spare leaves and use your Band-Aids as tape to stick the leaf over the wound</string>
    <string name="mus18_option2">Use your Band-Aids. </string>
    <string name="mus18_option3">Ignore it</string>

    <string name="mus19_main_text">You keep walking and eventually see a village.</string>
    <string name="mus19_option1">Enter the Village</string>
    <string name="mus19_option2">Go around the Village</string>
    <string name="mus19_option3">Let\'s go in!</string>

    <string name="mus20_main_text">You hide the cat from the man. But he sees it and attempts to fight you for him.</string>
    <string name="mus20_option1">Let the old man take him</string>
    <string name="mus20_option2">Run away with the cat</string>
    <string name="mus20_option3">Kill the old man</string>

    <string name="mus21_main_text">He thanks you for his cat and walks off.</string>
    <string name="mus21_option1">Feel amazing!</string>
    <string name="mus21_option2">Feel guilty for the cat</string>
    <string name="mus21_option3">Miss the cat</string>

    <string name="mus22_main_text">WHAT THE HECK? Dude thats seriously messed up. You have bad mental problems... Anyways you keep walking til you see a village... Don\'t do it...</string>
    <string name="mus22_option1">Do THIS?!? (Set fire to the Village)</string>
    <string name="mus22_option2">Im not doing anything (Enter Village)</string>
    <string name="mus22_option3">HAHA I LOVE MURDER! (Murder the entire Village)</string>

    <string name="mus23_main_text">You and your cat friend keep walking and eventually see a village.</string>
    <string name="mus23_option1">Enter the Village</string>
    <string name="mus23_option2">Go around the Village</string>
    <string name="mus23_option3">Call it quits and go home</string>

    <string name="mus24_main_text">What kind of person feels accomplished after doing that to the old man? You are a terrible person!</string>
    <string name="mus24_option1">Whatever</string>
    <string name="mus24_option2">Whatever</string>
    <string name="mus24_option3">Whatever</string>

    <string name="mus25_main_text">You hand him the corpse, he cries but thanks you for giving it to him.</string>
    <string name="mus25_option1">Feel good</string>
    <string name="mus25_option2">Feel sad for the old man</string>
    <string name="mus25_option3">Don\'t feel anything</string>

    <string name="mus26_main_text">You apply the leaf and feel its juices slipping into your bloodstream. The world seems different afterwards... But you keep walking and come upon a village</string>
    <string name="mus26_option1">Enter the Village</string>
    <string name="mus26_option2">Go around the Village</string>
    <string name="mus26_option3">Call it quits and go home</string>

    <string name="mus27_main_text">You apply the bandage and keep walking until you see a village.</string>
    <string name="mus27_option1">Enter the Village</string>
    <string name="mus27_option2">Go around the Village</string>
    <string name="mus27_option3">Call it quits and go home</string>

    <string name="mus28_main_text">You figure that it will heal itself and no need to waste Band-Aids or the leaf. You keep walking and come upon a village</string>
    <string name="mus28_option1">Enter the Village</string>
    <string name="mus28_option2">Go around the Village</string>
    <string name="mus28_option3">Call it quits and go home</string>

    <string name="mus29_main_text">You enter the village and are immediately greeted with gifts from the friendly natives. They offer you food, medicine, and a good nights sleep</string>
    <string name="mus29_option1">Accept the gifts</string>
    <string name="mus29_option2">Ignore the gifts and keep walking through the village</string>
    <string name="mus29_option3">I love gifts!</string>

    <string name="mus30_main_text">You successfully murdered everyone in the village... You are now a mass murderer... Did you ever think of the children in the village? Women and children! And you slaughtered them... I am ashamed. This was supposed to be a fun entertaining adventure but you turned it into the story of a psychopath... This is your last choice before you turn completely into a mass murderer... Choose wisely...</string>
    <string name="mus30_option1">Bury Everyone</string>
    <string name="mus30_option2">Spit on their bodies like the peasants they were</string>
    <string name="mus30_option3">Pet the ghost cat next to you</string>

    <string name="mus31_main_text">To continue on this path of the story you must spend $2.99. Or you can restart the story again.</string>
    <string name="mus31_option1">You got the PayWall ending</string>
    <string name="mus31_option2">You got the PayWall ending</string>
    <string name="mus31_option3">You got the PayWall ending</string>

    <string name="mus32_main_text">You and your cat enter the village. Everything seems quiet... All of a sudden you get jumped and a bag is thrown over your head.</string>
    <string name="mus32_option1">Fight!</string>
    <string name="mus32_option2">Let it happen</string>
    <string name="mus32_option3">Try to reason with them</string>

    <string name="mus33_main_text">You enter the village... For some reason you can\'t find anyone. Then you walk into what seems to be the town center. Everyone is kneeling before a statue that looks a lot like you... Wait a minute. That is you! The village people turn around and call out to you in their language. You don\'t know what they are saying but they all seem excited. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="mus33_option1">Aw heck no! (Run away)</string>
    <string name="mus33_option2">Let it happen</string>
    <string name="mus33_option3">Fight!</string>

    <string name="mus34_main_text">You keep moving, completely forgetting the village for better or for worse. You realize that you have not looked at your map in a while and seem to be lost... You have no idea where to go... Now what?</string>
    <string name="mus34_option1">Keep walking</string>
    <string name="mus34_option2">Stop and try to get your bearings</string>
    <string name="mus34_option3">Find your way home</string>

    <string name="mus35_main_text">You decide to accept the gifts. They are free after all? You spend the night but when you wake up in the morning you notice everything is quiet... too quiet...</string>
    <string name="mus35_option1">Go find out what happened</string>
    <string name="mus35_option2">Leave through the window and run away</string>
    <string name="mus35_option3">Keep sleeping</string>

    <string name="mus36_main_text">You decide that enough it enough and decide to go home. Your story ends. Your life has no meaning. How sad...</string>
    <string name="mus36_option1">You got the boring ending</string>
    <string name="mus36_option2">You got the boring ending</string>
    <string name="mus36_option3">You got the boring ending</string>

    <string name="mus37_main_text">You fight but with the bag over your head you don\'t seem to affect much. You blindly punch around until you get hit on the head and feel drowsy... You hear a faint meow before you pass out.</string>
    <string name="mus37_option1">Sleep... </string>
    <string name="mus37_option2">That sucks... </string>
    <string name="mus37_option3">Kitty!...</string>

    <string name="mus38_main_text">You let the villagers kidnap you. Knowing that there is no point to fighting. You hear your cat roar a meow, a fight of some sort and then silence. You hope that he is okay...</string>
    <string name="mus38_option1">Kitty!</string>
    <string name="mus38_option2">Get help Kitty!</string>
    <string name="mus38_option3">Run!</string>

    <string name="mus39_main_text">You run. And run. And run. And keep running til you cannot run no more. You are definitely lost and cannot gather where you are by looking at the map. What now?</string>
    <string name="mus39_option1">Start walking in a direction</string>
    <string name="mus39_option2">Gather your bearings</string>
    <string name="mus39_option3">Keep running</string>

    <string name="mus40_main_text">You let the villagers swarm you. They seem to be praising you. Anointing you in water, still repeating the same word over and over. You begin to realize that they think you are a god!</string>
    <string name="mus40_option1">I am a god!</string>
    <string name="mus40_option2">Accept their praises</string>
    <string name="mus40_option3">I am no god!! (Run away)</string>

    <string name="mus41_main_text">You stand your ground against the swarm of villagers. You wind up your fist and throw a punch at the man leading the swarm. All of a sudden everything turns white and your ears are ringing. When the effects fade you look around and see that all the villagers are gone. In their place is their clothes lying on the ground. No trace of them left...</string>
    <string name="mus41_option1">I am a god!</string>
    <string name="mus41_option2">Wait what?</string>
    <string name="mus41_option3">Who did this?</string>

    <string name="mus42_main_text">Wow, disrespecting their corpses? That is just rude now... You need some help... At this point I\'ve given up. You have ruined this game... Turned a nice fun action game into a horror game. A horror for everyone else that is!</string>
    <string name="mus42_option1">I love horror games!!</string>
    <string name="mus42_option2">(Recommended) WHO\'S NEXT?</string>
    <string name="mus42_option3">IM COMING FOR YOU NARRATOR!</string>

    <string name="mus43_main_text">Wait... Did you just pet nothing at your side? I think you are actually insane... At first i thought it was killing for enjoyment but now... Are you petting a hallucination?</string>
    <string name="mus43_option1"> I like kitties...</string>
    <string name="mus43_option2">He is so real!</string>
    <string name="mus43_option3">Real or not he is cute...</string>

    <string name="mus44_main_text">You decide to look around. You notice that there is a fire at the center of the village. You move slowly towards it and begin to hear crying. As you creep closer you begin to see the situation at hand. You see that all your villager friends are being held captive. Some of them are dead on the ground, including the tribe leader... There are about six masked men armed with spears and knives. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="mus44_option1">Lets fight!</string>
    <string name="mus44_option2">Use a distraction</string>
    <string name="mus44_option3">Run away!</string>

    <string name="mus45_main_text">You decide to go back to sleep........................ Until all of a sudden you feel a sharp pain. You wake up and see a masked man with a knife to your side. Actually it\'s in your side! He just stabbed you! You try to get up but the masked man puts you out of your misery...</string>
    <string name="mus45_option1">You got the death ending</string>
    <string name="mus45_option2">You got the death ending</string>
    <string name="mus45_option3">You got the death ending</string>

    <string name="mus46_main_text">You have walked for ages. Your feet are sore and you need to take a break.</string>
    <string name="mus46_option1">Take a break on the nearby rock</string>
    <string name="mus46_option2">Take a break on a nearby fallen tree</string>
    <string name="mus46_option3">Take a break on the ground</string>

    <string name="mus47_main_text">No matter what you do you cannot get your bearings...</string>
    <string name="mus47_option1">Keep walking</string>
    <string name="mus47_option2">Stop and try to get your bearings again...</string>
    <string name="mus47_option3">Find your way home</string>

    <string name="mus48_main_text">Really? I just told you that you can\'t get your bearings... Are you gonna keep trying?</string>
    <string name="mus48_option1">Keep walking</string>
    <string name="mus48_option2">Try to get your bearings again...</string>
    <string name="mus48_option3">Find your way home</string>

    <string name="mus49_main_text">Okay there is no point to this. Just keep walking! There is no point! Continue the story. Right now you are staring at a map looking confused and dumb... Keep walking!</string>
    <string name="mus49_option1">Keep walking</string>
    <string name="mus49_option2">Try to get your bearings again...</string>
    <string name="mus49_option3">Find your way home</string>

    <string name="mus50_main_text">FINE! Since you have no clue i\'ll tell you where to go! Just turn right and take 30 paces until you see a cave. Then enter it! Are you satisfied now?</string>
    <string name="mus50_option1">Thanks!</string>
    <string name="mus50_option2">Nah I don\'t trust you</string>
    <string name="mus50_option3">Try to get your bearings again...</string>

    <string name="mus51_main_text">You end up inside a hut with a weird looking man talking to you in a different language. You cannot understand what he is saying but it seems serious.</string>
    <string name="mus51_option1">Look confused</string>
    <string name="mus51_option2">Nod your head yes over and over...</string>
    <string name="mus51_option3">Look around the room</string>

    <string name="mus52_main_text">You start walking in a direction until you see a cave. You also hear a growling behind you. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="mus52_option1">Enter the cave</string>
    <string name="mus52_option2">Turn around</string>
    <string name="mus52_option3">Go home</string>

    <string name="mus53_main_text">You keep running and are still tired.</string>
    <string name="mus53_option1">Start walking in a direction</string>
    <string name="mus53_option2">Gather your bearings</string>
    <string name="mus53_option3">Keep running</string>

    <string name="mus54_main_text">You let the villagers worship you. They give you their best hut and you have servants whenever you need them for whatever you need them for. They teach you how to use your powers so that you can defend the village. A few weeks pass in your life of luxury. Then you remember the map.</string>
    <string name="mus54_option1">Forget the map</string>
    <string name="mus54_option2">Time to finish my quest!</string>
    <string name="mus54_option3">Enjoy the pleasures of being a god</string>

    <string name="mus55_main_text">After a while of pondering what happened. You decide to do some testing. You wind up and punch...</string>
    <string name="mus55_option1">A tree</string>
    <string name="mus55_option2">A rock</string>
    <string name="mus55_option3">Yourself</string>

    <string name="mus56_main_text">You think that someone else did this as there is no evidence towards you eliminating all the villagers. Despite the fact that you were the only survivor and the fact that you were the one who threw the first punch you somehow don\'t figure out it was you who threw the punch.</string>
    <string name="mus56_option1">Maybe it was me...</string>
    <string name="mus56_option2">It was definitely not me</string>
    <string name="mus56_option3">Maybe you are right</string>

    <string name="mus57_main_text">Well go play some horror game then! I recommend one that you don\'t end up being the killer cause you would have to much power. Try "Doki Doki Literature club". That game will scar you for life...</string>
    <string name="mus57_option1">You got the horror game ending</string>
    <string name="mus57_option2">You got the horror game ending</string>
    <string name="mus57_option3">You got the horror game ending</string>

    <string name="mus58_main_text">Just go to the cave... All i\'m saying</string>
    <string name="mus58_option1">Mmmmmm more blood!</string>
    <string name="mus58_option2">HAHA I LOVE MURDER!!</string>
    <string name="mus58_option3">I like dark places...</string>

    <string name="mus59_main_text">Haha good one. I\'m not in the same world as you idiot. I am currently in a room typing this into your game. There is absolutely no way... you... can... find.. me... Sorry someone is knocking at my door. I\'ll be back.</string>
    <string name="mus59_option1">You got the Narrator Death ending</string>
    <string name="mus59_option2">You got the Narrator Death ending</string>
    <string name="mus59_option3">You got the Narrator Death ending</string>

    <string name="mus60_main_text">Really? There is no cat! </string>
    <string name="mus60_option1">Talk to your cat army</string>
    <string name="mus60_option2">Give an inspirational speech to all your new cat friends</string>
    <string name="mus60_option3">Give your first command to your new army</string>

    <string name="mus61_main_text">You jump out of the bushes and punch the first masked man you see. He falls instantly.</string>
    <string name="mus61_option1">Keep fighting</string>
    <string name="mus61_option2">Rescue the villagers</string>
    <string name="mus61_option3">Run away!</string>

    <string name="mus62_main_text">You decide to look around for a distraction. You notice some gunpowder leading to a large barrel of it. You take out your lighter and light the gunpowder. You wait in the bushes until it explodes. Now what?</string>
    <string name="mus62_option1">Let\'s fight!</string>
    <string name="mus62_option2">Rescue the villagers</string>
    <string name="mus62_option3">Run away!</string>

    <string name="mus63_main_text">You decide to rest for a bit. </string>
    <string name="mus63_option1">Keep walking</string>
    <string name="mus63_option2">Try to get your bearings</string>
    <string name="mus63_option3">Go home</string>

    <string name="mus64_main_text">You follow the narrators instructions and find the cave after a while. As you are walking you hear something almost echoing your footsteps.</string>
    <string name="mus64_option1">Enter the cave</string>
    <string name="mus64_option2">Turn around</string>
    <string name="mus64_option3">Go home</string>

    <string name="mus65_main_text">You stand in one spot trying to get your bearings (since you don\'t trust me). After a while you begin to feel hungry, but because of your stubbornness you still try to gain your bearings. You eventually pass out and die of starvation. Serves you right.</string>
    <string name="mus65_option1">You got the stubborn ending</string>
    <string name="mus65_option2">You got the stubborn ending</string>
    <string name="mus65_option3">You got the stubborn ending</string>

    <string name="mus66_main_text">The chief notices how confused you look. He brings in a translator and he translates. Although the translator\'s english is not perfect. You get the gist that the village you are in is composed of people who were banned from society for eating cats.</string>
    <string name="mus66_option1">Kitty!</string>
    <string name="mus66_option2">Oh no...</string>
    <string name="mus66_option3">Im coming!</string>

    <string name="mus67_main_text">You look around and see a lot of cat pelts. It almost seems like the skin cats for a living...</string>
    <string name="mus67_option1">Kitty!</string>
    <string name="mus67_option2">Oh no...</string>
    <string name="mus67_option3">Im coming!</string>

    <string name="mus68_main_text">You enter the cave. Ignoring the thing behind you. As you walk into it you start to hear a person. The voice sounds familiar and as you move towards it you see who it is. Its STEVE!</string>
    <string name="mus68_option1">STEVE!</string>
    <string name="mus68_option2">The Janitor?</string>
    <string name="mus68_option3">I love Steve!</string>

    <string name="mus69_main_text">You turn around to confront the thing behind you. But before you can fully turn around you are tackled by a furry body. The thing that was making noises is on you! </string>
    <string name="mus69_option1">Throw it off and run into the cave</string>
    <string name="mus69_option2">Pet it</string>
    <string name="mus69_option3">Just Brush it off</string>

    <string name="mus70_main_text">You forget the map and continue to live your life of luxury. </string>
    <string name="mus70_option1">You got the luxury end</string>
    <string name="mus70_option2">You got the luxury end</string>
    <string name="mus70_option3">You got the luxury end</string>

    <string name="mus71_main_text">You remember the details about the map and head towards the cave where the X was. When you reach the cave you enter it and hear a voice.The voice sounds familiar and as you move towards it you see who it is. Its STEVE!</string>
    <string name="mus71_option1">Steve?</string>
    <string name="mus71_option2">The Janitor?</string>
    <string name="mus71_option3">The creepy guy?</string>

    <string name="mus72_main_text">You punch the tree and all of a sudden every tree in a quarter mile radius in the forest disappears...</string>
    <string name="mus72_option1">I am a superhero!</string>
    <string name="mus72_option2">I have powers!</string>
    <string name="mus72_option3">HECK YEAH!</string>

    <string name="mus73_main_text">You punch the rock and all surrounding rocks disappear including the one you punched...</string>
    <string name="mus73_option1">I am a superhero!</string>
    <string name="mus73_option2">I have powers!</string>
    <string name="mus73_option3">HECK YEAH!</string>

    <string name="mus74_main_text">You punch yourself and everything turns white. You are teleported into a world of white. You see some people off in the distance. You run to them and as you get closer you realize it is the villagers you made disappear. You stop running but it\'s too late. They have noticed you. They run at you but before you can start to run they tackle you and beat you to death...</string>
    <string name="mus74_option1">You got the death by villager ending</string>
    <string name="mus74_option2">You got the death by villager ending</string>
    <string name="mus74_option3">You got the death by villager ending</string>

    <string name="mus75_main_text">Okay... sure... You feel no guilt about eliminating an entire race because it was not you who did it.</string>
    <string name="mus75_option1">Yup!</string>
    <string name="mus75_option2">Maybe I do have powers...</string>
    <string name="mus75_option3">Well I should catch the person that did this!</string>

    <string name="mus76_main_text">Did you just talk to those invisible cats? And you told them to eliminate all humans?!?! I cannot even comprehend what is happening</string>
    <string name="mus76_option1">The cats will rule!!</string>
    <string name="mus76_option2">Long live cats</string>
    <string name="mus76_option3">I am the ghost cat god!</string>

    <string name="mus77_main_text">You walk to the cave and enter it... You hear a voice...</string>
    <string name="mus77_option1">KILL!</string>
    <string name="mus77_option2">YOU WILL DIE!</string>
    <string name="mus77_option3">HAHA I LOVE MURDER!!</string>

    <string name="mus78_main_text">You punch the next masked man. He does not fall as easy but you still win. </string>
    <string name="mus78_option1">Keep fighting</string>
    <string name="mus78_option2">Rescue the villagers</string>
    <string name="mus78_option3">Run away!</string>

    <string name="mus79_main_text">You attempt to rescue the villagers but the masked men do not let you. They capture you while you tried to untie a villager. When you wake up you find yourself tied to a stake over a fire...</string>
    <string name="mus79_option1">You got the cannibal ending</string>
    <string name="mus79_option2">You got the cannibal ending</string>
    <string name="mus79_option3">You got the cannibal ending</string>

    <string name="mus80_main_text">You attempt to rescue the villagers. You succeed to untie most of them before the masked men see you. You leave a few villagers behind but the rest of them run with you from the village.</string>
    <string name="mus80_option1">Run to the cave</string>
    <string name="mus80_option2"></string>
    <string name="mus80_option3"></string>

    <string name="mus81_main_text">You leap out of your seat and run out of the hut. You look around for kitty. But he is nowhere to be seen.</string>
    <string name="mus81_option1">Check a nearby hut</string>
    <string name="mus81_option2">Look around more</string>
    <string name="mus81_option3">Look inside a nearby sack</string>

    <string name="mus82_main_text">You now know the extent of your powers. You realize you can become the greatest superhero ever.</string>
    <string name="mus82_option1">To the cave!</string>
    <string name="mus82_option2"></string>
    <string name="mus82_option3"></string>

    <string name="mus83_main_text">You spend the rest of your days searching for the person that murdered the entire village. You never find him/her.</string>
    <string name="mus83_option1">You got the idiot ending</string>
    <string name="mus83_option2">You got the idiot ending</string>
    <string name="mus83_option3">You got the idiot ending</string>

    <string name="mus84_main_text">You just sent a bunch of non existent beings to... wait a minute... What is happening!? Cars are driving off the roads! People have scratch marks all over them! You monster! You did this. I\'m going to end this before it gets worse!</string>
    <string name="mus84_option1">No you don\'t!!</string>
    <string name="mus84_option2">Get him cats!</string>
    <string name="mus84_option3">Sick em!</string>

    <string name="mus85_main_text">You run into the cave... Knife in hand (How did you get that?). As you run in you see a man. ITS STEVE!</string>
    <string name="mus85_option1">KILL!</string>
    <string name="mus85_option2">Wait...</string>
    <string name="mus85_option3">HAHA I LOVE MURDER!!</string>

    <string name="mus86_main_text">You and the villagers run into the nearby cave. You hear a voice and run to it in hopes of finding someone to help all of you. As you get closer you see who it is. ITS STEVE!</string>
    <string name="mus86_option1">Steve?</string>
    <string name="mus86_option2">Help us Steve!</string>
    <string name="mus86_option3">Janitor?</string>

    <string name="mus87_main_text">You found him! Kitty looks unconscious so you grab him and run out of the village. Never looking back.</string>
    <string name="mus87_option1">Run into a nearby cave</string>
    <string name="mus87_option2"></string>
    <string name="mus87_option3"></string>

    <string name="mus88_main_text">You run into a nearby cave with Kitty in your arms. You hear a voice. Maybe it\'s someone who will help you! As you get closer you see who it is. ITS STEVE!</string>
    <string name="mus88_option1">Steve?</string>
    <string name="mus88_option2">The Janitor?</string>
    <string name="mus88_option3">Help us Steve!</string>

    <string name="mus89_main_text">You instantly stab Steve before he explains anything. He mutters "why" before he collapses. You stab him repeatedly even after he has died... I don\'t know why you did this. You ruined the entire storyline of this game. If you really want to know what happens after this, nothing happens. You become a murderer of everything in the forest. No one knows about you. No one cares about you. You just kill everything and eat all the animals you killed. Somehow you found enjoyment out of this ending... I didn\'t... I am disappointed.</string>
    <string name="mus89_option1">You got the disappointment ending</string>
    <string name="mus89_option2">You got the disappointment ending</string>
    <string name="mus89_option3">You got the disappointment ending</string>

    <string name="mus90_main_text">You stop your murderous tendancies for one second and listen to Steve. He explains to you that he memorized the map you carried when you dropped it. He tells you that he still has no found the treasure... As he looks at you he notices the blood... He sees the knife in hand... He starts to run... But you don\'t let him. You scream bloody murder and chase after him. Once you do, you stab him repeatedly. You keep stabbing, and stabbing... and stabbing... </string>
    <string name="mus90_option1">You got the stabbing ending</string>
    <string name="mus90_option2">You got the stabbing ending</string>
    <string name="mus90_option3">You got the stabbing ending</string>

    <string name="mus91_main_text">Steve explains to you that when he briefly saw the map he decided to go to the X himself. You see him carrying a gauntlet of some sort. It has 5 gems on the fingers and one central gem in the middle. He claims that he is the god of the universe. He raises his hand into a position where he could snap his fingers instantly.</string>
    <string name="mus91_option1">Let him snap</string>
    <string name="mus91_option2">Not on my watch!</string>
    <string name="mus91_option3">Run away!</string>

    <string name="mus92_main_text">You keep punch the next masked men but he overpowers you. You fail to save the villagers.</string>
    <string name="mus92_option1">You got the failure ending</string>
    <string name="mus92_option2">You got the failure ending</string>
    <string name="mus92_option3">You got the failure ending</string>

    <string name="mus93_main_text">As you inch closer, Steve notices you. He explains to you how he memorized the map when you dropped it. He went his own way to the X. You see something shiny behind him. You ask what it is. Steve tells you that its his! And that you cannot have it!</string>
    <string name="mus93_option1">Fight him for it</string>
    <string name="mus93_option2">Let him have it</string>
    <string name="mus93_option3">Run away</string>

    <string name="mus94_main_text">You throw a punch at Steve but he dodges. Steve winds up a punch...</string>
    <string name="mus94_option1">Block</string>
    <string name="mus94_option2">Punch</string>
    <string name="mus94_option3">Kick</string>

    <string name="mus95_main_text">You let Steve have whatever it is. You head home and forget about the day.</string>
    <string name="mus95_option1">You got the nice? ending</string>
    <string name="mus95_option2">You got the nice? ending</string>
    <string name="mus95_option3">You got the nice? ending</string>

    <string name="mus96_main_text">You run away from creepy janitor Steve. Later that week you hear that Steve has been fired for stealing gold from the school. Turns out that thing he was hidding was the school\'s secret stash of gold. You never hear of Steve again and live the rest of your life normally.</string>
    <string name="mus96_option1">You got the fired ending</string>
    <string name="mus96_option2">You got the fired ending</string>
    <string name="mus96_option3">You got the fired ending</string>

    <string name="mus97_main_text">You block his punch successfully.</string>
    <string name="mus97_option1">Punch</string>
    <string name="mus97_option2">Block your face</string>
    <string name="mus97_option3"></string>

    <string name="mus98_main_text">You attack him as he attacks you. Both of you hit each other and fall on the ground. You both get up after a certain amount of time... Look at each other.</string>
    <string name="mus98_option1">Fight!</string>
    <string name="mus98_option2">Run away</string>
    <string name="mus98_option3">Talk about your feelings</string>

    <string name="mus99_main_text">You and Steve sit down and talk about your feelings. You discuss Steve\'s past life with how he used to be in the Navy. He tells you about the horrible shark attacks that he witnessed. And how his best freind died from one of them. You comfort him. Both of you become good freinds and forget about the treasure. You leave it behind and go back to school knowing you have made a friend along the way.</string>
    <string name="mus99_option1">You got the friend ending</string>
    <string name="mus99_option2">You got the friend ending</string>
    <string name="mus99_option3">You got the friend ending</string>

    <string name="mus100_main_text">You throw a punch at Steve and it connects. He falls on the ground. You broke his nose.</string>
    <string name="mus100_option1">Take the treasure</string>
    <string name="mus100_option2">Sit down next to Steve</string>
    <string name="mus100_option3">Get help</string>

    <string name="mus101_main_text">You block nothing and Steve talks advantage of your blindness and runs away with the treasure. Nice...</string>
    <string name="mus101_option1">You got the Nice... ending</string>
    <string name="mus101_option2">You got the Nice... ending</string>
    <string name="mus101_option3">You got the Nice... ending</string>

    <string name="mus102_main_text">You run up to the treasure and take it. You grab as much as you can but you cannot carry it all. You leave the cave with arms full of gold and diamonds. When you get home you hid them all under your bed and sell the gold and diamonds in a way so that you do not look suspicous. You become a billionaire and live out the rest of your days in a mansion.</string>
    <string name="mus102_option1">You got the rich ending</string>
    <string name="mus102_option2">You got the rich ending</string>
    <string name="mus102_option3">You got the rich ending</string>

    <string name="mus103_main_text">You run and get help but by the time you come back Steve is gone and so is the treasure...</string>
    <string name="mus103_option1">You got the "DANG YOU STEVE!" ending</string>
    <string name="mus103_option2">You got the "DANG YOU STEVE!" ending</string>
    <string name="mus103_option3">You got the "DANG YOU STEVE!" ending</string>

    <string name="mus104_main_text">You pet the animal. It purrs... Its another cat!!! </string>
    <string name="mus104_option1">I love kitties!</string>
    <string name="mus104_option2">Kitten!</string>
    <string name="mus104_option3">Kitty!</string>

    <string name="mus105_main_text">You cannot stop me now! Im going to.. Wait no! Stop! It hurts! You won\'t... get away.. with this...</string>
    <string name="mus105_option1">You got the "I just did" ending</string>
    <string name="mus105_option2">You got the "I just did" ending</string>
    <string name="mus105_option3">You got the "I just did" ending</string>

    <string name="mus106_main_text">As you run to Steve he starts to laugh... mainically... You and the villagers start to slow down. When you stop you notice the masked men are behind you. You are between the masked men and Steve, and by the looks of it, Steve does not want to help. </string>
    <string name="mus106_option1">Let\'s go out with style!</string>
    <string name="mus106_option2">Try to talk to Steve</string>
    <string name="mus106_option3">This is the end</string>

    <string name="mus107_main_text">You do not even try to negoitiate with Steve. You and the villagers go into fight mode. You fight the masked men and Steve. You and the villagers seem to be losing the battle. But as time goes on it seems to be evening out until its just you and Steve.</string>
    <string name="mus107_option1">Let\'s do this</string>
    <string name="mus107_option2">Let\'s fight</string>
    <string name="mus107_option3">You are going down Janitor</string>

    <string name="mus108_main_text">You try to talk to Steve. Steve explains to you that he memorized the map and followed it to the red X. He says that he will have the item and no one else will take it! He charges at you and the fight begins between you and the villagers, Steve and the masked men. You and the villagers seem to be losing the battle. But as time goes on it seems to be evening out until its just you and Steve.</string>
    <string name="mus108_option1">Let\'s do this</string>
    <string name="mus108_option2">Let\'s fight</string>
    <string name="mus108_option3">You are going down Janitor</string>

    <string name="mus109_main_text">You do not even try to fight. You turn around and see the masked men putting bags over the villagers heads. You turn around to look back at Steve and he is gone. Eventually they get to you and knock you out before they put the bag over your head.</string>
    <string name="mus109_option1">Dang</string>
    <string name="mus109_option2"></string>
    <string name="mus109_option3"></string>

    <string name="mus110_main_text">You wake up back at home.. Maybe it was all a dream... Or not? You will never know...</string>
    <string name="mus110_option1">You got the "Dream?" ending</string>
    <string name="mus110_option2">You got the "Dream?" ending</string>
    <string name="mus110_option3">You got the "Dream?" ending</string>

    <string name="mus111_main_text">Steve explains to you that when he saw the dropped map, he had memorized it and decided to claim the treasure for himself. As he does this Kitty wakes up and seems fine. Steve notices the cat but does not say anything about it. Instead he tells you that he will not let you take the treasure from him. He pulls out a knife.</string>
    <string name="mus111_option1">Fight!</string>
    <string name="mus111_option2">Runaway</string>
    <string name="mus111_option3">The treasure is mine!</string>

    <string name="mus112_main_text">You and Kitty prepare to fight. Steve swings with his knife but misses. Kitty runs up and scratches his ankles. Steve grabs his ankle in pain. What do you do?</string>
    <string name="mus112_option1">Punch!</string>
    <string name="mus112_option2">Kick!</string>
    <string name="mus112_option3">Let the cat deal with Steve</string>

    <string name="mus113_main_text">You and Kitty run away and head towards your home. You will never forget that day. You and Kitty become best friends and you look forward to seeing him everyday after school.</string>
    <string name="mus113_option1">You got the safe cat ending</string>
    <string name="mus113_option2">You got the safe cat ending</string>
    <string name="mus113_option3">You got the safe cat ending</string>

    <string name="mus114_main_text">You attack Steve as he grabs his ankle instantly putting Steve on the ground in tremoundous pain. You and the kitty run over to the treasure and grab what you can. You both runaway from the cave and head home. Over time you slowly sell the treasure and become a billionare. You and the cat become best friends and live out the rest of your life retired and in a mansion. </string>
    <string name="mus114_option1">You got the teamwork ending...</string>
    <string name="mus114_option2">You got the teamwork ending...</string>
    <string name="mus114_option3">You got the teamwork ending...</string>

    <string name="mus115_main_text">You yell and swing at Steve. You miss.</string>
    <string name="mus115_option1">Block</string>
    <string name="mus115_option2">Swing again</string>
    <string name="mus115_option3">Recover footing</string>

    <string name="mus116_main_text">You block immediately after your miss and just in time. You block a punch from Steve.</string>
    <string name="mus116_option1">Punch</string>
    <string name="mus116_option2">Block</string>
    <string name="mus116_option3"></string>

    <string name="mus117_main_text">You attempt to swing again but before you can start Steve punches you. You fall on the ground...</string>
    <string name="mus117_option1">Keep fighting</string>
    <string name="mus117_option2">I don\'t give up easily</string>
    <string name="mus117_option3">I give up</string>

    <string name="mus118_main_text">You attempt to recover your footing but Steve punches you. You fall on the ground.</string>
    <string name="mus118_option1">Keep fighting</string>
    <string name="mus118_option2">I don\'t give up easily</string>
    <string name="mus118_option3">I give up</string>

    <string name="mus119_main_text">You punch Steve but he somehow blocks it.</string>
    <string name="mus119_option1">Kick him</string>
    <string name="mus119_option2">Punch again</string>
    <string name="mus119_option3">Block</string>

    <string name="mus120_main_text">Steve stands over your pathetic body. He kicks you once more for good measure and runs off. You are beaten and pass out. When you wake up you are in the hospital. You immediately tell the doctors your story but they believe you hit your head hard and are imagining things. Maybe you are... You live out the rest of your life in a mental asylum trying to tell everyone your story but no one believes you.</string>
    <string name="mus120_option1">You got the asylum ending</string>
    <string name="mus120_option2">You got the asylum ending</string>
    <string name="mus120_option3">You got the asylum ending</string>

    <string name="mus121_main_text">You block your face. Blinding yourself from Steve\'s next attack. Which was a kick. You fall on the ground...</string>
    <string name="mus121_option1">Keep fighting</string>
    <string name="mus121_option2">I don\'t give up easily</string>
    <string name="mus121_option3">I give up</string>

    <string name="mus122_main_text">You kick him where he is not blocking and it makes contact. But Steve recovers quickly...</string>
    <string name="mus122_option1">Block</string>
    <string name="mus122_option2">Punch</string>
    <string name="mus122_option3">Recover footing</string>

    <string name="mus123_main_text">You block his punch successfully.</string>
    <string name="mus123_option1">Punch</string>
    <string name="mus123_option2">Block</string>
    <string name="mus123_option3">Kick</string>

    <string name="mus124_main_text">You attack Steve and this time it knocks him down. He cries for mercy. You leave him be and go take the treasure. Which was only a GameBoy Advanced... Was it worth it? That\'s for you to decide while you play Pet Shop.</string>
    <string name="mus124_option1">You got the "Hard work, Little Gain" ending</string>
    <string name="mus124_option2">You got the "Hard work, Little Gain" ending</string>
    <string name="mus124_option3">You got the "Hard work, Little Gain" ending</string>

    <string name="mus125_main_text">Steve snaps his fingers... Suddenly you don\'t feel so good... You slowly disappear...</string>
    <string name="mus125_option1">You got the meme ending</string>
    <string name="mus125_option2">You got the meme ending</string>
    <string name="mus125_option3">You got the meme ending</string>

    <string name="mus126_main_text">You throw a punch at Steve. It misses but it distracts him from snapping his fingers.</string>
    <string name="mus126_option1">Time to fly!!!</string>
    <string name="mus126_option2">Keep swinging</string>
    <string name="mus126_option3">Go invisible</string>

    <string name="mus127_main_text">You run away from Steve trying to avoid the snap. You hear the snap... As you head home you call for you mom. But she does not exist... You look at the news and see that 3.5 million people have disappeared from the earth... Now what?</string>
    <string name="mus127_option1">You got the "Infinity War" ending</string>
    <string name="mus127_option2">You got the "Infinity War" ending</string>
    <string name="mus127_option3">You got the "Infinity War" ending</string>


    <string name="mus128_main_text">You all of a sudden start flying. You circle Steve and swing in from all angles. He reverts time to when he was in his snap position. </string>
    <string name="mus128_option1">Fly</string>
    <string name="mus128_option2">Punch</string>
    <string name="mus128_option3">Go invisible</string>

    <string name="mus129_main_text">You keep swinging at Steve. He reverts time to when he was in his snap position.</string>
    <string name="mus129_option1">Fly</string>
    <string name="mus129_option2">Punch</string>
    <string name="mus129_option3">Go invisible</string>

    <string name="mus130_main_text">You go invisible. He does not see you. You swing and miss. He reverts time back to when he was in his snap position</string>
    <string name="mus130_option1">Fly</string>
    <string name="mus130_option2">Punch</string>
    <string name="mus130_option3">Go invisible</string>

    <string name="mus131_main_text">You start to fly again. But he knows you can do this and delivers a power punch to your stomach. You fall on the ground. Steve begins to snap his fingers again.</string>
    <string name="mus131_option1">Get up and punch</string>
    <string name="mus131_option2">Run away</string>
    <string name="mus131_option3"></string>

    <string name="mus132_main_text">You throw a punch and it barely misses. Should have taken boxing classes...</string>
    <string name="mus132_option1">Kick him</string>
    <string name="mus132_option2">Use your hidden power!</string>
    <string name="mus132_option3"></string>

    <string name="mus133_main_text">You find out that you can turn invisible. But Steve bends reality so that he can see you. He punches you in the gut.</string>
    <string name="mus133_option1">Get up and punch</string>
    <string name="mus133_option2">Run away</string>
    <string name="mus133_option3"></string>

    <string name="mus134_main_text">You go invisible again. But of course Steve knows this and starts blindly swinging until he hits you. You fall on the floor. Steve raises his hand to the snap position.</string>
    <string name="mus134_option1">Get up and punch</string>
    <string name="mus134_option2">Run away</string>
    <string name="mus134_option3"></string>

    <string name="mus135_main_text">You attempt a kick but it fails, miserably. You tear your achilles tendon. You no longer can walk and therefore Steve snaps his fingers. Everything goes white...</string>
    <string name="mus135_option1">You got the stupid ending</string>
    <string name="mus135_option2">You got the stupid ending</string>
    <string name="mus135_option3">You got the stupid ending</string>

    <string name="mus136_main_text">You reach inside your mind... You search for the hidden power within yourself... You find it. You aim it at steve and activate it. Steve dies instantly. You have saved the world. Using... A gun... What do you do now?</string>
    <string name="mus136_option1">You got the cliffhanger ending. Wait til the second game to fulfill this.</string>
    <string name="mus136_option2"></string>
    <string name="mus136_option3"></string>

</resources>